Chapter 1269: Nan Qizi and Old Man Fu

The elderly man coughed before replying, "I had no choice in the matter. Zhang Kui insisted on getting me to come here as our newest member is apparently a cultivation prodigy who's already mastered the third layer of the Vajra Arts despite his young age."

"The third layer of the Vajra Arts?! Him?" Xiang'er's eyes widened with shock.

"Don't be rude, Sister Xiang'er; invite Daoist Priest Nan Qizi and Old Man Fu into the carriage," Liu'er instructed.

Xiang'er immediately stepped aside to allow the two men into the carriage as she apologized, "Ah, please forgive me for my rudeness."

The Daoist priest merely smiled in response before entering the carriage. In contrast, Old Man Fu heaved a faint sigh before slowly making his way into the carriage as well.

At this point, the light in the sky was already beginning to fade, yet the squad was still traveling full speed ahead with no intention of stopping at all.

"This is the man that Benefactor Zhang was referring to, right?" The Daoist priest turned his gaze toward Han Li as soon as he entered the carriage.

"Indeed, I am the new recruit that Brother Zhang was referring to. I appreciate your visit, but I'm afraid that you'll most likely be powerless to remedy my condition as well. I'll be able to recover after a few months of rest and recuperation," Han Li replied in a calm voice.

Nan Qizi wasn't irked by Han Li's rejection. Instead, he merely put on a faint smile, and said, "Hehe, you've already mastered the third layer of the Vajra Arts, so your powers are not inferior to mine. However, there are many differences between cultivators and body refinement warriors like you. Perhaps I'll be able to find a way to reduce the time required for you to make a full recovery."

A hint of surprise flashed through Han Li's eyes upon hearing this.

Even though his spiritual sense was unable to leave his body, thereby rendering him unable to ascertain the Daoist priest's cultivation base, in such close quarters, Han Li was still able to determine that this man was a Foundation Establishment cultivator.

In the human world, all cultivators looked down on mortals as if they were mere ants, and even Qi Condensation cultivators despised mortals as if they were an inferior species. However, this Foundation Establishment Daoist priest was the first cultivator he had encountered in this world, and he was conversing in such a polite manner with a "mortal" like him. This type of interaction struck Han Li with a rather peculiar feeling.

It appeared that the Endless Sky Beast hadn't been exaggerating about the power of the mortals in the Spirit Realm.

With that in mind, Han Li nodded with a polite smile, and said, "In that case, I'll have to trouble you to conduct a thorough examination."

Nan Qizi nodded with a smile before raising a hand to reveal an azure bracelet around his wrist. He laid his other hand on the bracelet, upon which a copper mirror appeared in his hand.

Han Li stirred slightly upon seeing this.

That bracelet appeared to be a storage treasure, one that was clearly of a far higher caliber than his storage pouches. If even a Foundation Establishment cultivator possessed such a treasure, then they were most likely very prevalent here in the Spirit Realm. As such, it was most likely the case that storage pouches weren't used at all in the Spirit Realm.

Aside from his two Immortal Vanquishing Beads, Han Li had stored all of his treasures into his storage pouches prior to dissipating his Nascent Soul. After that, he had buried those storage pouches along with his spirit beast pouches over 100 feet deep into the ground.

As a safety precaution, he had also opened a few of the spirit beast pouches to release his Gold Devouring Beetles, Six-Winged Frost Centipedes, and Weeping Soul Beast to dwell underground, and he had commanded them to guard his storage pouches.

As for that Armored Earth Dragon, Han Li didn't even take it with him to the Spirit Realm. Instead, he had left it with Nangong Wan.

As such, aside from his Immortal Vanquishing Beads, the invisible Spiritform Talisman, and his Law Destruction Eye that could be hidden within his body, all of his treasures had been left in the desert, including his Heavenvoid Cauldron and Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords. He was unable to use any magic power at the moment, so those treasures would be useless to him. Carrying those treasures with him would only get him killed, so he would simply have to recover them after he regained his ability to use his magic power. The desert was an extremely barren place, so his storage pouches should be safe there, particularly with his spirit beasts looking after them.

As for that mysterious little green vial, Han Li had thought about it for a long while before deciding to keep it with him. The vial had no features to suggest that it was anything out of the ordinary, so it would simply be regarded as an ordinary vial even if someone were to discover it.

Nan Qizi was naturally unaware of what Han Li was thinking, and he was certainly oblivious to the fact that Han Li was a Deity Transformation cultivator. As such, he merely asked a few questions to assist in making his diagnosis before waving his copper mirror toward Han Li.

A swath of azure light flew forth from the mirror, enshrouding most of Han Li's body. Nan Qizi then closed eyes, appearing as if he were trying to sense something through the use of the treasure in his hand. After a while, a hint of surprise appeared on the Foundation Establishment cultivator's face. A short while later, he opened his eyes again and appraised Han Li with a rather peculiar expression.

"What is it?" Han Li asked.

"Benefactor Han, I suggest you take better care of yourself. I can see that many of your meridians are damaged, which suggests to me that either insufficient spiritual Qi was injected into your body during your cultivation of the Vajra Arts, or you didn't have enough pills to assist you during that process. Us humans don't have powerful bodies from birth like demon beasts do, so we have to be extremely careful when refining our bodies. Thankfully, the damage is not irreversible and your meridians appear to be healing. However, such injuries are indeed quite difficult to recover from, and I don't have any effective treatment method I can suggest, nor any suitable pills I can offer. The only thing I can do is to craft a few pain-killing talismans for you to make the recovery process easier to bear," Nan Qizi replied with a wry smile.

"Then I'll have to thank you in advance for your efforts," Han Li said with a smile.

"Hehe, seeing as Daoist Priest Nan Qizi has already examined you, it doesn't really matter whether I have a look or not. However, that Zhang brat asked me to come, so I can hardly leave without doing anything," the white-robed elderly man mused.

"You're far too modest, Benefactor Fu. The Profound Golden Needle Techniques passed down in the Fu Family have saved countless lives, and even many cultivators have benefitted from it. I'm sure you'd be far more capable than I am when it comes to remedying Benefactor Han's condition," the monk replied modestly.

"I'm just an in-name disciple of the Fu Family, so I know nothing about the Profound Golden Needle Techniques. You have far too high an opinion of me, Daoist Priest Nan Qizi." The elderly man shook his head in response.

Nan Qizi merely chuckled and stepped aside.

The white-robed elderly man stepped forward and took his place by Han Li's side.

He raised a hand and grabbed one of Han Li's wrists, then raised his other hand into the air as several streaks of golden light shot forth.

The golden light revealed themselves to be thin golden needles that embedded themselves into Han Li's body.

Han Li was completely unable to move a moment ago, but as soon as those needles entered his body, he sprang up into a sitting position like a jack-in-the-box.

"Liu’er get something for him to lean on." The elderly man issued a calm instruction to the girl in blue.

"Yes, Old Man Fu. Xiang'er, grab some blankets and tuck them behind his back," Liu'er instructed.

Xiang'er faltered slightly upon hearing this, seemingly quite reluctant to use her blankets as a backrest for Han Li, but she still did as she was told in the end.

Meanwhile, the elderly took a seat beside Han Li, closing his eyes as he laid a hand over Han Li's wrist to examine his pulse.

Han Li looked at the elderly man in silence, and he could sense a feeble flow of energy rapidly traveling through various parts of his body.

If it weren't for the fact that spiritual sense was extremely powerful, it really would've been quite difficult to detect that flow of energy.

The elderly man seemed to have sensed Han Li's scrutiny, and he opened his eyes to find Han Li looking at him with a hint of a smile on his face.

At this moment, Xiang'er had already carried a stack of blankets over to them. Before the elderly man had to say anything, she had already tucked the blankets behind Han Li's back.

Han Li rested his back against the blankets, and was greeted by a faint fragrant scent as he extended words of gratitude toward Xiang'er.

In response, Xiang'er merely gave a clipped reply that was neither cold nor pleasant.

Han Li paid no heed to her attitude as he continued to scrutinize the elderly man.

At this moment, Old Man Fu waved a hand through the air, and another golden needle appeared in his palm. This was one slightly longer than the ones already embedded in Han Li's body.

The elderly man expertly tightened two fingers around the needle before his arm transformed into a blur as he rapidly pierced the needle into various parts of Han Li's body in quick succession.

Han Li felt as if countless acupoints in his body had been pierced in unison.

A throbbing sensation then began to flow through his limbs, and Han Li discovered that he was able to slowly raise his arms.

Everyone drew a sharp breath in unison upon seeing this. Not only were the four young women's eyes filled with admiration, Nan Qizi was also quite impressed.

"As expected, the Profound Golden Needle Techniques of the Fu Family really are quite extraordinary!" the Daoist priest chuckled.

"It's nothing much. All I did was temporarily restore a certain degree of mobility to his limbs. However, you still can't use any strength or your meridians could be ruptured on a large scale," the elderly man warned with a stern expression.

"Thank you, Old Man Fu!" Han Li was ecstatic as he flexed his fingers.

He had learned similar needle techniques in the human world, and he had thought himself to be somewhat of an expert in this art, but he couldn't even hold a candle to this Old Man Fu. It was amazing to think that someone really could create such miracles with needle techniques alone.

However, his heart jolted upon hearing the cautionary words that the elderly man extended toward him.

Upon verifying that Han Li was indeed able to move his limbs again, Old Man Fu waved a hand toward Han Li, upon which golden light flashed and all of the needles extricated themselves from within Han Li's body before disappearing up the elderly man's sleeve.

Han Li slowly lowered himself down from the bench and took a few tentative steps.

"That's all I can do for you; you'll have to recover your meridians on your own. I still have some matters to attend to, so I won't stay here any longer." The elderly man rose to his feet and prepared to depart.

Nan Qizi nodded upon hearing this, and he pulled out several talismans before waving a hand through the air. All of those talismans then transformed into streaks of azure light that disappeared into Han Li's body.

Immediately thereafter, the Daoist priest also stood up to leave.

Thus, the four young women accompanied them out of the carriage before closing the door again.

At this moment, Han Li had sat down in a chair with his eyes closed, seemingly experiencing the effect of the talismans within his body.

The four young women glanced at one another after returning to the carriage before Liu'er suddenly smiled, and asked, "Brother Han, have you really mastered the third layer of the Vajra Arts?"

"I was merely lucky," Han Li replied in an ambiguous manner.

Chapter 1272: Demon Serpent

Under the spell formation’s effects, the situation reversed. It appeared they could hold out for a while longer.

But just as Han Li was wordlessly watching the battle, something unexpected occurred.

Following a loud bang, an explosion occurred near the three women. A demon beast with a serpent’s body and a human head shot out from the sand.

The demon serpent had a head of sickly yellow hair and a hideous woman’s face. A pair of delicate infant-white arms emerged from its side, each holding a meter-long bone spear. Black Qi wrapped around the spears, revealing themselves to be low-grade magic tools.

As soon as the demon serpent appeared, the three women controlling the formation turned pale with fright. The demon serpent turned to look at the women in charge of the formation and flashed a malevolent smile and wordlessly waved her spears. Three black lights streaked from the spear and flew towards the women.

The three were quick to react. They immediately recovered from their shock and took out the flags from the formation, hastily waving it in front of them.

Several crackles sounded as a wave of mist suddenly appeared in front of them.

The black lights flew into the mist, resulting in three large explosions. The mist scattered from the strike but managed to block the attack for Xiang’er and the white-robed woman. However, the red-robed woman’s mist was far weaker. When the black light struck the mist, her body trembled and she flew out into the air, away from the mist’s protection.

The red-robed woman knew things were far from good and she turned deathly pale. For a time, she wasn’t able to control her own body.

When the demon serpent saw this, it smashed down its tail and its body blurred, arriving below her with its spear held out.

The other two women yelled out but they weren’t able to protect her.

In the following moment, the woman was about to be stabbed by the glowing black bone spear.

But at that moment, a piercing sound whistled through the air. A white object struck the spear with strange accuracy.

Bang. The spear was pushed a half-foot away, brushing past the woman’s clothes. The woman was left deathly pale with her brush from death, but she used the opportunity to regain control of her body. With a flip, she nimbly landed on the ground.

The white object was an unremarkable stone.

The demon serpent was surprised, but malevolent glint flashed from its eye and with its other arm, it released a chain of stabs.

However, yet another whistling sound shrieked through the air. This time, a stone didn’t strike the spear but pounded towards the demon serpent’s head.

The stone clearly carried an immense strength. If the attack truly struck the serpent, it might not shatter its skull, but it would be enough to leave it dazed at the very least.

The demon serpent was enraged and had no choice but to turn its head to the side and use its spear and block the oncoming stone.

But with a muffled thump, the serpent felt a huge force knock against its hand, forcing it back several steps. Enraged, it turned to look in the direction where the stone came from.

A young man was looking down at it from the top of a nearby tortoise carriage. He was fiddling with a similar stone in his hand.

It was Han Li.

The red-robed woman had now arrived next to her companions in a blur and let out a sigh of relief.

Having been foiled twice, the serpent felt immense rage and opened its mouth to release a black poisonous mist towards the three women.

But then, Nan Qizi’s voice sounded from one of the carriages, “Evil creature! You dare?!”

Soon after, the white light shot out from the carriage window. It circled once in the air before cleaving at the demon. It was a crystalline sword that was several inches large.

When the serpent saw this, its expression changed and it ceased spitting its poison. It rushed to toss the spear in its hand with all its strength at the carriage it came from. It then twisted its body to duck into the sand.

When it saw more cultivators appear, it didn’t dare to fight and immediately flee.

As for the spear, it was aimed at Han Li.

Obviously, the demon thought to take revenge on the mortal that thought to ruin its fun and express its resentment.

When Han Li saw the black light coming towards him, he wryly smiled. Not only did he not use the stone in his hand, but he also stood still in place.

Boom. The spear struck Han Li accurately, and he was sent flying over thirty meters away, leaving a large hole in a carriage’s container he fell on. The crash resulted in twinkling blades falling out from a carriage’s storage.

“Ah!”

When the three women saw this, they let out a cry of alarm. As for Nan Qizi, he let out a yelp from a neighboring carriage.

Afterwards, Nan Qizi’s small sword circled in the air before turning to him.

At that moment, the red-robed woman shook her flag and scattered her protective mist, then running over to the container.

“Brother Han, are... are you alright!?” She worryingly cried out.

A trace of worry also appeared on the other two women’s faces.

“I am well. However, my body can’t seem to move.” Han Li spoke out with a wry chuckle.

The three women were relieved to hear this and exchanged a glance. They all jumped on top of the giant tortoise in question and looked at the damaged container.

They saw Han Li lying down on a pile of spears and sabers with town robes. He appeared helpless, but there were no obvious injuries.

The three were overjoyed and dragged him out in a joint effort.

“Brother Han, thank you for saving my life!” The red-robed woman gratefully said.

Han Li chuckled and casually answered, “It wasn’t much. It only took a slight effort. However, the attack has left me helpless. I’ll have to lay down for a moment longer.”

A trace of surprise appeared on his face and Nan Qizi smiled, saying, “There is nothing wrong. The Vajra Arts is worthy of being of the five great body refining techniques. You are already so strong after cultivating the third layer. That evil creature’s magic tool wasn’t what harmed Benefactor Han, but the exertion of the rock throwing has caused some injury to your meridians. It should be healed with some rest.”

“I am glad!” The red-robed woman said with joy.

Nan Qizi smiled and looked at the formation diagram that no longer glowed with light. He chuckled and said with a deeper tone, “How could this humble Daoist lie? However, the situation will turn for the worse now that you’ve stopped driving the Minor Returning Spring Formation.”

When that was said, the three’s expression vastly changed and they hastily looked around them. They saw that the guards have become exhausted once more without the aid of the formation, and they have resumed taking casualties.

“Damn. We’ve only brought one copy of the formation diagram. We’ve used all the power from our formation flags to block the demon serpent. We won’t be able to activate it again.” The white-robed woman cried out.

The other two looked at each other in dismay.

“That is truly troublesome!” The Daoist priest frowned. As they thought of a plan, they suddenly heard the sounds of battle around them stop. Suddenly, the guards let out a resounding cheer.

The women looked around in surprise. They saw that the huge worms were jumping off the carriages and fleeing in a panic. They seemed to have lost all their previous mettle.

“It is done! Sister Liu’er and the others must’ve defeated the insect demons.” The green-robed woman said with a grin. The other two also wore pleasant expressions.

As expected, several tens of cavalry were returning to the caravan, leaving dust clouds in their wake.

Out of the fifty-some cavalry that went out on the attack, only about thirty managed to return. Furthermore, many of them were injured and stained with blood. It was clear they had a desperate battle.

When the wolf-mounted cavalry returned, the large scarred man tossed something on the ground. It was the head of a huge worm, but its body was entirely golden.

The blue-robed woman leading the crimson tiger appeared entirely without injury.

When the two saw Nan Qizi and the three women surrounding Han Li, they revealed a trace of shock.

At that moment, one of the guards gave a detailed explanation of what happened.

The scarred man soon let out a bellow, it appears that I’ve made the right decision to take you into our organization. As soon as you joined, you already saved Quan’er. If something truly happened, I wouldn’t have the face to see the mistress.”

When the blue-robed woman heard this, she looked at Han Li with a friendly face.

Han Li simply smiled back and said nothing else.

Since they repelled the Sandbug Beasts, the troops needed to rest. After half a day, they resumed their journey.

The rest of the way was remarkably peaceful. After three days, the caravan left the Azure Sifting Desert and was met with an endless grassland. It was incredibly flat.

With this, the speed of the caravan increased several times as the tortoises could walk with bigger steps.

As for Han Li, he remained still on his back, unable to move. He later noticed that the banter from the caravan instantly went silent after they entered the grassland.

In addition, the four women sitting the carriage looked at the grassland with an uneasy expression, faintly betraying a sense of dread.

Chapter 1278: The Gold Jade School

Han Li looked at the two with narrow eyes.

The two clearly weren’t ordinary body refiners as demonstrated from the chilling pressure of their gaze. He did sense the two appeared to be stronger than Zhang Kui.

“Elder Brothers, I am Brother Han, who recently joined the enterprise. The mistress mentioned she wished to see me.”

The shorter of the two glanced at Han Li and said, “Ah, you are the person who cultivated the Vajra Arts to the third stage. You do appear young, but is that from taking a medicine pill to maintain your appearance?”

The words contained were actually rather rude.

“If you two feel that way, then consider it to be true.” Han Li’s heart jumped, but he maintained a smile on his face.

The larger of the two then snorted and harshly said, “I don’t believe you truly cultivated the Vajra Arts to the third layer. I’ll be testing you, don’t take offense.” With a cold glint shining from his eye, he grabbed Han Li’s wrist.

Han Li raised his brow but didn’t avoid the large man’s hand. When the man touched his wrist, he sensed the man’s fingers turn exceptionally cold and release a huge force squeezing his wrist.

Han Li wore neither a scowl or a smile, but his eyes turned sullen.

Under the man’s force, Han Li’s wrist glowed with a layer of faint golden light, but it soon disappeared. Soon, Han Li remained still and allowed the man to do as he wished.

A short moment later, the large man exerted a large portion of his strength but Han Li still remained nonchalant. Eventually, the man’s face revealed surprise, and he hesitated for a moment. But rather than letting go, he took a deep breath and shined black light from his fingers, exerting even more strength on Han Li’s wrist.

The smile Han Li wore on his face finally vanished and he snorted, giving a casual shake of his twist.

The large man suddenly felt a vibration run through his fingers as his body became numb. Then with a frightened cry, he felt a huge force travel through him as he flew into the air.

As Han Li wore an emotionless expression, the large man was flung into a stone wall nearby. Just as the man was about to have a messy impact, the other guard suddenly pounced ten meters to quickly catch him.

But just as the shorter guard caught his companion in midair, his expression vastly changed and he reached out to grab him with his other hand.

A large thump sounded, followed by two softer thuds.

Although the shorter guard was able to catch him, he staggered back eight steps and his complexion was pale.

Han Li narrowed his eyes and glanced at the shorter guard.

Even against the huge force Han Li released, the shorter guard was still able to catch his companion. The shorter guard’s body refinement technique must be the greater of the two.

The youth surnamed Luo was left stunned.

The two men at the gate were Mistress Fang’s personal bodyguards. Although they normally didn’t mingle with the cavalrymen, they possessed brilliant body refinement techniques to the point where Captain Zhang Kui held them in secret admiration. When the confident cavalrymen thought to test their skill against them, they all suffered a miserable defeat.

As for Han Li who recently joined them, he was able to turn them pale with a flick of his wrist. They weren’t able to resist in the slightest.

Was the third layer of the Vajra Arts alone able to produce this much strength?

Youth Luo’s expression wavered at the slightest.

He couldn't have known that most of Han Li’s strength actually stemmed from the many Dragon Scale Fruits he consumed over hundreds of years and Bone Tempering Art. Otherwise, even as powerful as the third layer of the Vajra Arts may be, he would only be able to produce enough strength to rival the two men. Besides, in truth, Han Li cultivated the Vajra Arts to the fourth layer.

The shorter guard circulated his inner body techniques several times before eventually swallowing his frustration. With a calmed expression, he said, “Brother Han possesses exceptional abilities. We concede defeat. Please head in.” He couldn't help but look at Han Li with a trace of respect.

As for the taller guard that Han Li tossed, his expression turned unsightly.

Han Li smiled and gave them a short salute before casually strolling in.

Youth Luo naturally didn’t have the qualifications to follow him and could only wait outside.

When Han Li saw that the main gate to the courtyard building was shut and thought to knock on it, he heard a woman’s sweet voice sound from within.

“Young Sir Han, please come in. I’ve been waiting on you for quite a while.”

Han Li blinked twice and calmly walked in, not feeling particularly surprised.

When he went in, his expression stirred.

He was surprised to see several people in the room.

In the master’s seat across from the door sat an azure-robed woman in her thirties. Her skin was fair and her beauty was still present. Behind her stood a blue-robed man that was in his mid-twenties. He bore a strong resemblance to the woman.

Sitting across from the woman was an embroidered-robed man with a young face and grey hair. He wore an indifferent expression.

Sitting at his side was a handsome young man and a beautiful young woman.

They seemed to know what happened outside the courtyard gate and looked in Han Li’s direction when he entered.

The azure-robed woman had a trace of delight on her face and the blue-robed youth appeared curious. As for the embroidered-robed man, he was wearing a frown and the young pair simply looked surprised.

The azure-robed woman stood up and curtsied him, “Young Sir Han, I hope you don’t take offense. My bodyguards tested you on my orders. I simply wished to know if the third layer of the Vajra Arts was as fearsome as the rumors said. The technique is widely spread, but it is one of the most difficult body refining techniques to cultivate. Very few people break through to the second layer, let alone the third like you.”

Han Li casually asked with a smile, “I am already a member of your enterprise. I can’t take offense over a trifling test. Are you pleased his by my performance?”

Although he planned on concealing himself in the Heavenly East Enterprise as an insignificant character, he didn’t mind revealing a portion of his true strength.

As of current, Mistress Fang was looking at him in a favorable light.

When she heard Han Li’s reply she sweetly smiled and said, “The third layer of the Vajra Arts far exceeded my expectations. You’ve opened my eyes. Ah yes, I should give Young Sir Han an introduction. This is my son, Pan Qing. He is cultivating Immortal techniques under the Golden Jade Sect. These three are Immortal masters, fellow sect members of my son.”

“So they were Immortal masters!” Han Li saluted them.

Although his spiritual sense couldn't leave his body, it was still quite sharp and sense their cultivation at this distance. They were all at Foundation Establishment-stage and above. However, the youth and the other young pair appeared to have achieved Foundation Establishment recently as their spiritual Qi was still quite weak. As for the embroidered-robed man, his magic power was quite dense so he should be at false core stage, the peak of Foundation Establishment.

With the abilities Han Li showed previously, they didn't dare to treat him light and returned the greeting.

The embroidered-robed man even smiled and said, “Although I haven’t cultivated body refinement techniques before, my master fought against a high-grade body refiner in the past. It is rumored that person was able to slay several grade six and seven demon beasts by himself. I originally believed them to be fanciful tales, but from what Brother Han displayed, I am convinced they are true. But from the force Han Li displayed, it shouldn’t only be a result of the Vajra Arts but his nature or divine power as well.”

This person was quite experienced to see some oddities from Han Li’s immense strength.

Of course, Han Li wasn’t about to reveal the Dragon Scale Fruit and all else. He gave a simple explanation, “Brother Qin is quite sharp. Some of my power comes from an innate nature.”

The embroidered-man nodded, feeling that most of his suspicions had disappeared.

Following that, the embroidered man said nothing else. Rather, Mistress Fang had a friendly chat with Han Li, but when she asked about his origins, Han Li gave a vague answer.

Mistress Fang didn’t pursue the matter when she saw this and instead informed him that Pan Qing and the others were to assist An Yuan City with the beast torrent on orders from their master. The upper echelons of An Yuan City had ties to the Gold Jade Sect. The sect would send out low-grade cultivators to use the beast torrent as an opportunity to make breakthroughs. The Foundation Establishment cultivators were likely sent for this reason as well.

Of course, the Gold Jade Sect wasn’t the only sect that sent disciples over to the city. There were at least a dozen more.

When the men of the Heavenly East Enterprise entered An Yuan City, they were also conscripted to fight against the beast torrent as per law. As such, Mistress Fang had Han Li act as Zhang Kui’s second in directing the guards.

When Han Li heard her, he nodded in agreement after brief consideration.

When Mistress Fang saw this, she wore a satisfied expression and had Han Li depart. According to what she said, the beast torrent could start at any time. Furthermore, it would be a grand beast torrent consisting of several types. It would be best for Han Li to rest and hone his spirit.

Han Li smiled and promptly left the room.

When the door was shut, Mistress Fang’s smile vanished and was replaced with hesitation.

The embroidered-robed man stroked his chin and asked, “What? Does Mistress Fang feel this person is a rare find and has changed her mind?”

Mistress Fang frowned and openly expressed her thoughts, “That is so. This person is young, yet holds his current cultivation. If he were nurtured, I suspect that he will become an existence on the level of Old Fire. Otherwise, I would’ve gone with the original plan and have Zhang Kui or the Liu Brothers follow you on your journey after the beast torrent .”

Chapter 1280: Wild Beast Torrent (1)

Han Li felt his heart roil.

When he heard him mention 'silver wolves', he was instantly reminded of Silvermoon.

She was a giant silver wolf that hailed from the Silvermoon Wolf Clan. Perhaps the silver wolves were of the same clan.

But regardless of whether this was true, it was no use to him in his current realm. He could only set aside the thought in the back of his mind.

Zhang Kui solemnly said, "If it were only common wolves, we wouldn't have anything to fear with our high walls, but unfortunately, they are being led by intelligent low-grade demon beasts.

They are also mixed with variant beasts that are halfway to becoming a demon beast. While the variant beasts don’t possess the same inconceivable abilities as demon beasts, they are still far more fearsome than any ordinary beast. The size, power, and vicious far exceed their ordinary kind. At the very least, an ordinary low-grade body refiner wouldn’t be able to take one alone.”

"How troublesome! Are there many of these variant beasts in the wave?"

Zhang Kui pondered briefly and doubtfully said, "There is about one variant beast in a thousand."

"A thousand?" Han Li swept his eyes past the azure beast sea and couldn't help but wryly laugh.

Even if he couldn't guess their number, they numbered in the millions at the very least. There should be several thousand variant beasts among them. And with no Core Formation cultivators guarding the city, those numbers could prove fatal.

After taking another look, Zhang Kui sighed, clearly discouraged by the sight, and said, "Alright, let's go to other areas and take a look at the other beasts."

Although Han Li followed the large man through the city, he still wore a smile and asked, "What, Brother Zhang worries the city defenses won't hold?"

Zhang Kui replied with an anxious expression, "I am worried, yes. I've seen several beast torrent s in the past, but never against a city that was just established in the last thousand years. Against a grand beast torrent like this one and with our lacking preparations, they should be able to breach our defenses.

Furthermore, this beast torrent also has Leocon Beasts. Although there won’t be too many of them, they will all be grade one demon beasts. As we won’t be able to protect against them, they will be a large threat to the city.

“Are Leocon Beast s so fearsome?” A glint flashed in Han Li’s eyes and his voice carried doubt.

“ Leocon Beast s aren’t considered strong amongst the rank of demon birds, but they carry a formidable toxin that can kill ordinary people. Unless they approach us, we will only be able to attack them from afar. And even worse is how nimble and quick these birds are. While they may be lacking in strength, they are unable to suppress them as they attack the weakest points in the city’s defense.

With a tone of surprise, Han Li asked, “How did this lack of aerial power come to be? Could it be the An Yuan City Lord didn’t know this matter would be so critical?

From what he came to know, all positions of secular power within the city belonged to mortals.

“Even if he knew about it, what could he do? I heard the last beast torrent to attack the city left disastrous damage. Their numbers were almost exhausted. Being able to restore their defensive strength to this level had already exhausted the city lord’s influence. The other nearby cities also lent them a few weapons and soldiers. There is nothing else he can do about the air.”

When Han Li heard this, he was at a loss for words.

Not long after, Han Li followed Zhang Kui to another side of the city wall and saw rows of meter-long pythons forming a red beast sea. It appeared even more fearsome than the sea of wolves.

The only good news to hear from this was that these snakes weren’t venomous. As such, their defenses were more lax towards them.

As Han Li gazed at the sea of pythons from a distance, he would occasionally spot pythons that were several times larger than the others and he inwardly gasped.

These variant pythons were over thirty meters long, no smaller than a crimson wyrm. They could easily devour a man. And because the hoard of crimson pythons was larger than the azure wolves, it was only natural there would be more of variants.

After looking at these two beast hoards, Han Li felt some regret at not being able to see the Leocon Beast s.

According to what the Zhang Kui said, the hawks were perched at a concealed area. They wouldn’t show themselves until it was time to attack.

As Han Li looked at the distant pythons, he suddenly asked, “Why haven’t the beast hoards launched their attacks?”

“The beast hoards are led by intelligent demon beasts. They won’t attack us of their own accord. They will be certain to cooperate with the other two demon hoards in a joint assault and strain our forces. Normally, something like this will only occur for another day. Let’s go. We need to lead the Heavenly East Enterprise soldiers to the center of the city in preparation for orders. If we are lucky enough to make a breakthrough or comprehend something, it may be worth it to put ourselves in danger.” Zhang Kui let out a cold laugh and led Han Li back to the inn.

As expected, the guards at the inn had received orders from An Yuan City and were preparing to move out. They were already gathered together.

The Gold Jade Sect cultivators were asked for their presence earlier and had already left.

Without any hesitation Zhang Kui immediately shouted and commanded the two hundred soldiers of the Heavenly East Enterprise to move out, marching out of the inn in a powerful display.

When they arrived on the street, they saw private troops and body refiners head in the direction of the palace, but most of these groups were nowhere as large or formidable as the Heavenly East Enterprise. Their numbers ranged anywhere from five or six to a dozen.

As Han Li traveled together with the others, they caught quite a bit of attention, particularly with the fifty mounted horned wolves.

After all, the horned wolves were one of the many beasts that were tamed by the humans of the spirit realm. Each one was meticulously raised from birth, completely erasing their savage nature. As they were able to exhibit greater power when joined together with cavalrymen, their price was considerably high.

Only a business as overbearing at the Heavenly East Enterprise had the ability to purchase so many trained horned wolves for their guards.

All the people on the streets were heading in the direction of a huge plaza near a city wall. The city was facing the hoard of azure wolves.

Tens of thousands of empty-handed strong men, a few uniformed troops, and scattered body refiners were already gathered together. There were even a few mounted horned wolves there, but their numbers didn’t match the cavalrymen of the Heavenly East Enterprise. Surrounding the plaza were a few fully-armed An Yuan City guards keeping order.

A silver-armored middle-aged man stood at the other end of the plaza. He was speaking with a Confucian scholar and a Buddhist monk at his side.

When Han Li saw this person, he recognized him as the officer he had seen watching the gate.

The scholar and the monk were the two cultivators that inspected their troops. The silver-armored middle-aged man had some sort of skill to keep behind the two cultivators.

At that moment, the silver-armored man noticed that enough people had gathered together and he waved his arm.

The soldiers behind him roared, utter a string of orders that were already prepared.

The first order was to organize a division of cavalrymen. Afterwards, a group of land tortoise carriages rushed into the plaza, carrying a large quantity of weapons and some armor. They began to distribute them to the strong men.

As for the body refiners, they didn’t hold common weapons in their eye and they stood in place with a detached gaze.

For the time being, private troops such as Han Li and the lone body refiners remained to the side.

Then, the private troops and body refiners were bewildered by the long wolf cries outside the city. They were resounding and harsh as if brimming with violent energy.

Han Li narrowed his eyes when he heard this. The myriad of wolf howls soared through the heavens like rumbling thunder.

The body refiners were better off with only changes in expression, but the commoners felt overwhelmed as the scream filled the world.

But that was only the start. They soon heard hissing and strange bird cries from other directions.

Although these sounds weren’t as overwhelming as the wolf howls, they still sent shivers down people’s spines.

At that moment, gongs sounded from all the city walls at nearly the same time. A man’s voice then filled the air. It wasn’t particularly loud, but it reached the ears of everyone in the plaza, “Be Careful, the beasts have begun to move.” It was a sound transmission that came from a grey-robed Foundation Establishment cultivator riding on a flying sword. There appeared to be other flying cultivators giving warnings throughout different districts of the city.

Suddenly, an uproar rose through An Yuan City and squads of idle soldiers sprung into action. They immediately scaled the walls, manned the ballistas, and readied themselves for battle.

Chapter 1292: Yu Yang City

Forty years is enough time for a soft baby to turn into a strong man, and for a child with spirit roots to become a low or mid-grade cultivator. But in the scope of an ancient city that existed for over a million years, it may as well happen over the blink of an eye.

When the three human territories were formed, Yu Yang City was the first founded in the Heavenly Origin Region.

Although it was only a medium-grade city and the city lords had no plan for expansion, it repelled every beast torrent easily. Never once did it encounter great danger.

This was because Yu Yang City was one of the most populated cities with body refiners. It carried this reputation throughout the Heavenly Origin City.

It was said that the current Heavenly Origin Sage had cultivated the body refinement technique to perfection in the city, leaving behind a grand history there.

The city housed countless body refinement sects and schools. High-grade body refiners rare in other areas were present in the city in large numbers. At the heart of the city, there was even a ‘sacred tower’ that stored the collections and experiences of body refinement sects. The collection was so expansive and detailed that it was renowned as one of the best in the region.

With such things located in the city, it attracted more low and mid-grade body refiners each year. Against such a formidable fighting force, a trifling beast torrent posed no threat.

Apart from this, Yu Yang City had a reputation for creating spirit tools on par with Heavenly Origin City. Each year a large number of spirit tools were refined there and purchased by merchants and body refiners alike.

Several auction houses greatly profited in selling rare spirit tools.

These auction houses more or less held a large number of spirit tool master smiths.

The so-called spirit tool masters were akin to pill refinement masters and spell formation masters as a master of their craft.

However, these people were peculiar where they needed to refine body refinement techniques to a certain extent and acquire some understanding of spell formations as well. Furthermore, they also required a naturally powerful spiritual sense.

With these conditions, one can become a spirit tool master. Those who wish to become one would need immense amounts of practice in addition to their natural talents.

The spirit tool masters held by the auction houses were all excellent and produced spirit tools with great power and inconceivable abilities.

Of course, these spirit tools were also meticulously forged. It commonly took several months to refine one, and when their extraordinary abilities were displayed in an auction house, they were sold at sky-high prices.

The Long Xing Auction House was one of the largest in Yu Yang City. They abruptly emerged and created a reputation that rivaled long-established auction houses.

The master of this auction house quickly became someone of considerable status in the city.

But one day in the Long Xing Auction House, a fat man wearing extravagant robes was pacing back and forth in the main hall.

He occasionally looked in the direction of the entrance with worry.

Another moment later, the fat man came to stop and loudly yelled, “Feng Er! Go take another look outside and see if Grandmaster Han has arrived.”

“Yes, milord!”

A young man hastily acknowledged his order and ran off, his footsteps quickly becoming faint.

The fat man paced for a moment more. Then, he seemed to tire and sat down, the chain creeping from his weight.

The fat man didn’t fear that that chair would collapse. Rather, he simply took a teapot from the table and poured himself a few cups in an easy manner.

“Could it be Brother Fan’s temper is a result of illness?” A clear voice sounded from the direction of the door, followed by the owner’s appearance.

When the fat man saw the newly arrived man, he immediately stood up, and the rolls of fat underneath his chin shook from his laughter, “Brother Han, you’ve finally arrived. Feng Er, that idiot didn’t inform me of your arrival.”

“Don’t blame him, I had him keep watch outside.”

The person who arrived appeared to be a common middle-aged man. He had creases on his brow and long black facial hair. As he carried a long bundle in his arms, he looked at the fat man with a mysterious smile.

It appeared the two were quite familiar with one another.

“Haha, although I know Brother Han never missed an appointment, this matter is quite important. This is related to my efforts in the city for the last several tens of years, so I was quite worried. This is the item that Brother Han personally forged?” The fat man looked at the middle-aged man’s bundle with excitement.

“That’s right. Old Brother Fan should take a look at it. The middle-aged man smiled and handed over the bundle. Then he took a seat at a nearby chair.

The old fat man took the long bundle and began to quickly tear off the cover, revealing a meter-long sword covered in a faint golden sheath. The sword was embedded with three spirit stones of various colors. At a glance, one could tell it was an unordinary spirit tool.

When the fat man saw this, he grasped the sword handle carefully and slowly took it out of the sheath.

A ring akin to the dragon’s cry sounded and a ball of golden light appeared before the fat man. It turned into a small golden wyrm that twirled in front of him.

The fat man glanced at the light and shook the sword sheath. As soon as the wyrm vanished, a glistening golden sword with a wyrm pattern appeared in his hand.

“Marvelous, marvelous! This is the sole top-grade spirit tool that emerged within Yu Yang City within the last hundred years. It possesses the inconceivable ability to take another form. Hehe, with this word, the others won’t dare to compete with me. Big Brother Han, you’ve helped this little brother tremendously.” The fat man sheathed the sword and broke out into bellowing laughter.

The middle-aged man sipped on the tea, revealing not a trace of excitement, “It was nothing. I was only able to refine the spirit tool because of the materials you’ve supplied me. Otherwise, I wouldn’t have been able to refine it no matter the skill.”

“Hehe, that is so, Big Brother! Those with empty reputations can’t hope to compare with you,” The fat man laughed.

“There is no need to flatter me. That sword is the last spirit tool I’ll make for you. In a moment, I will depart from the city. I reckon I won’t return.” The middle-aged man spoke with a smile.

The fat man woke up from his glee and hastily said, “Big Brother, what are you saying? Why do you want to leave the city? Could it be the subordinates I’ve assigned to you? Give the word and I will immediately cut them off and assign you better ones.”

The middle-aged man slowly said, “In the past, I made an error in my cultivation and you happened to pass by and lend me a hand. I was also unable to safely break through my bottleneck at the time. Now that several decades have passed and I forged all these spirit tools for you while hiding my identity, I have fully paid back your kindness. Now, the Long Xing Auction House has become one of the largest in the city. After you present that sword to the city lord, I’m sure it will be the largest for sure. I wasn’t able to fully teach my techniques to the apprentices you gave to me, but they know enough to continue your auction house. You should know I fully intend to cultivating body refinement techniques. Forging spirit tools was something I only did in passing. I won’t gain anything else from staying here.”

“Could it be Brother Han’s cultivation has reached another bottleneck?” When the fat man’s heart jumped when he heard Han Li’s final sentence.

The middle-aged man simply replied with a silent smile.

The fat man was stunned.

While others might now know of this person’s formidable power, the fat man clearly understood it.

Ten years ago, he came across danger and this good friend of his saved him. In a single breath, he killed a dozen low-grade body refiners that invaded his mansion. He displayed fearsome cultivation that was no weaker than a high-grade body refiner. Now that he has encountered another bottleneck, his cultivation will greatly progress after he breaks through it. At that moment, Brother Han’s cultivation will reach an inconceivable stage.

“Old Brother Fan, it is good that you know. I must thank you for keeping quiet about me and purchasing large quantities of techniques and medicine pills on my behalf. However, we must now part. I can only bid you farewell!” With that said, the middle-aged man stood up and saluted him, walking out without turning back.

The fat man’s lips quivered, but eventually, he couldn't come up with any words to convince him to stay. He could only watch the middle-aged man walk away with a dim face.

When the fat man saved Brother Han, it was the biggest turning point in his life. With all his power, Brother Han supported the nameless merchant until he became one of the leading figures in Yu Yang City. But now that Brother Han felt that he paid back his kindness in full, he walked away without any hesitation.

Naturally, he couldn't tell him to stay.

Outside the Long Xing Auction House, the middle-aged man saddled on a deer-like mount and made his way to the city exit.

Several hours later, the middle-aged man appeared on a cliff many kilometers away from the city. He looked at the tremendous city in the distance and leaped off the deer, sweeping his sleeve past his face.

An inconceivable event occurred.

After his sleeve fell, his facial hair disappeared and his middle-aged face turned young, turning into a youth that appeared to be in his late teens.

He was Han Li, who was last seen with the Gold Jade Sect Cultivators to seize the treasure.

Han Li indifferently glanced at the city walls from a distance and he suddenly turned around. Leaving behind the deer, the strode in the distance.

Not long after, he turned into a black dot on the horizon and disappeared into the wilderness.

Chapter 1295: Heavenly Origin Martial Equipment

“The Setting Sun Tomb!”

Demon and human alike called this place by that name.

To tell the truth, during ancient times, there weren't seven suns, but nine. But when the human and demon clans had first arrived in the spirit realm, an enormous battle swept through most of the races in the spirit realm.

Hundreds of characters with cultivation comparable to those in the Immortal realm battled throughout the spirit realm for an unknown reason.

As a result, not only did the weak perish, but vast lands, mountains, and seas underwent amazing changes, splitting the earth itself and destroying two of the suns.

It was said that one of the suns descended here, resulting in an enormous depression in the ground.

However, flying across this so-called depression would take a high-grade cultivator at least a year to fly through, even by using the full power of their magic treasures. The depressing itself contained countless mountain ranges and tens of giant lakes that spanned myriads of kilometers, not to mention anything of the forests and plains it contained.

It is said that even if ten million cultivators were to enter the Setting Sun Tomb, they would only amount to a drop in a vast ocean.

Such a large region naturally had a few human settlements on its border. One of the more well-known settlements was the cultivator controlled giant scale city “Setting Sun City”.

The city was constructed close to the Setting Sun Tomb. Although it was about the same in size to other cultivator cities, many mid and high-grade cultivators appeared there, ranking it among the top three cities in the Heavenly Origin Region. In addition to the cultivators there, there were also a large number of high-grade body refiners.

The body refiners possessed strength that was equivalent to the power of Foundation Establishment and Core Formation cultivators, but their number was at least ten times greater.

If it weren’t for the pitifully few numbers of peak grade body refiners and the Deity Transformation-stage cultivators present in the city, it would be difficult to call it a cultivator city.

But funnily enough, on the other side of the Setting Sun City in the demon lands, there was a city by the same name that was established by demon cultivators.

It was said the demon city was even larger than the human’s Setting Sun City.

High-grade demon cultivators gathered there in droves. There were even powerful human cultivators that went over to observe the city from a distance and gave honest descriptions of it.

However, Han Li held little interest towards the demon city.

At that moment, he was walking down one of the streets in the human Setting Sun City and was looking at the tidy tall stores to either side of him with an odd expression on his face.

This was just a common street in the city and the shopkeepers of these stores weren’t Qi Condensation cultivators, but low-grade body refiners.

The items being sold in this store ranged from demon beast materials to magic and spirit tools. There was a wide assortment of items, but there were no stores that specialized in selling common mortal items.

Not long after Han Li entered the gates of Setting Sun City, he walked down several streets and found a different scene each time.

This city was enormous. Even with a vast number of cultivators and body refiners, a majority of the people in the city were mortals. In fact, they lined the streets and could be spotted everywhere. However, they were all robust men and were exceptionally busy, running errands for cultivators and body refiners alike.

When Han Li turned a corner, he swept his gaze and suddenly found himself looking at a skinny man letting loose spittle on a group of people.

The man was a Qi Condensation cultivator and he was talking down to a group of common mortals. They looked miserable in the face of the cultivator’s torrent of words.

“Do you not know that this fanged beast pounced at my head as soon as it saw me. I, an Immortal master, with a mere sweep of his hand, released my Black Cloud Sword and easily lopped off its two claws. My magic tool can be exchanged for ten mid-grade spirit stones. Although it is only a low-grade magic tool, its might... Huh, who are you?” When a hand pressed on the skinny man’s shoulder, he hastily yelped and turned around, discovering a young man looking at him with a beaming smile.

Just as the skinny man thought to rebuke him, he noticed that the golden sparkling ring on Han Li’s finger. He then wore a forced smile and asked, “My name is Tiang Xing. Is there anything I can help you with?”

Body refiners that could wear spirit rings weren’t ordinary folk. They possessed power at mid-grade or higher. They weren’t someone that a trifling Qi Condensation cultivator could provoke.

“My name is Han,” Han Li calmly said, “I just saw how happy you were chatting and it seemed that you know much about the city. I hoped you could answer a few of my questions or even be my guide for a few days if that’s possible.”

The skinny man’s face lit up and he said, “So it turned out that Brother Han has just arrived in this city. Well, you found the right person! While I won’t say that I know everything about this city, I did live here for a few decades. But might I ask how you plan on employing me?”

Han Li rubbed his chin and bluntly proposed, “I’ll give you ten spirit stones for each day.”

The skinny man took a close look at Han Li and then smiled, saying, “That is too little. Please give me a bit more. I am a cultivator too. I can get that number of spirit stones by fetching spirit medicines outside.”

Han Li snorted. Although he disliked fussing over little matters, he didn’t want the skinny man to be greedy and bluntly said, “Ten spirit stones is already much. Let’s see you find some spirit medicines outside and not be afraid of being a demon beast’s dinner. I’ll give you twenty spirit stones and that will be all.”

“Alright, I agree! You lot can continue talking. This Immortal master and I will be heading out first.” Seeing that Han Li was unhappy, the skinny man quickly agreed and waved his hand to the others behind him.

When the mortals heard this, they immediately dispersed.

“May I ask where you wish to go?” The skinny man cautiously asked while attempting to guess Han Li’s strength.

Body refiners and cultivators differed. A body refiner’s cultivation depended on the hardiness of their body. It couldn't be determined with spiritual sense.

Han Li turned around and spoke without looking at him. “First bring me to the nearby spirit tool and materials shops. Give me an introduction to the city as well.”

The skinny man quickly followed after Han Li and eloquently spoke, “That will be no problem. Setting Sun City has eight main districts. Three of them are occupied by ordinary people. Five of them are the shops and quarters for body refiners and cultivators. However, there are a few differences in these five districts.

In four of them, including this one, everyone can sell and buy as they please. But in the fifth district, everyone must pay a spirit stone to be present there. It is the center of Setting Sun City.

Be it quality spirit tools or top-grade treasures, they are all exchanged in the heart of the city. Most of the large businesses in the Heavenly Origin Region are also gathered there. I heard even spirit treasures are sold there.”

“Spirit treasures?” Han Li’s heart stirred, but he maintained a calm expression, “I don’t care about those. Tell me about other things.”

“That is so. Information on spirit treasures won’t do much for you. On the other hand, these businesses will have many top-grade spirit tools for sale. Ah yes, there is some information you might be interested in, Brother Han. I heard that one of the auction houses acquired a set of martial tools that the Heavenly Origin Sage used back when, calling them the Heavenly Origin Martial Equipment. They are preparing to bid them off.

The set has five items, each a top-grade article equivalent to a cultivator’s magic treasure. It is said that these spirit tools can be used to cultivate a body refiner’s body with a different, more powerful strength. This was before the Heavenly Origin Sage cultivated spirit roots and still managed to slay many formidable enemies. When this information spread out, many high-grade body refiners stayed in the city, preparing to join in the auction.” The skinny’s man’s words caused Han Li to stop in his tracks.

“The Heavenly Origin Martial Equipment! It truly has such wondrous abilities?” Han Li finally showed his interest.

“It should prove true. These are words that the auction released.” The skinny man pledged, slapping his chest.

After a moment of silence, Han Li asked, “When does the auction start?”

“Although they didn’t give any concrete dates, it should be in four months at the latest. The auction doesn’t dare to keep so many high-grade body refiners waiting.” When the skinny man heard this, his heart trembled. Could it be he came across a stroke of luck? The person before him was a high-grade body refiner. Although he possessed a young face, he might have preserved his appearance with a medicine pill.

As Han Li thought of this, Tian Xing became unconsciously reserved.

In the following moment, Han Li asked a few more questions about the Heavenly Origin Martial Equipment. Furthermore, he also inquired about other areas in the city.

Although feeling somewhat bewildered, the skinny man answered all of Han Li’s questions and led Han Li down several streets until they arrived at a store specialized in spirit tools and their materials.

Although he heard that the top-grade items were being sold in the heart of the city, he didn’t plan to immediately head there.

Although spirit tools and their materials were considered rare, they were still far more common than materials needed for magic and ancient treasures. It was also possible he wouldn’t be able to find suitable spirit tool materials if he looked at a place specializing in selling higher quality goods.

Of course, they would have top-grade spirit tools without a doubt.

When Han Li walked into the store, he felt his spirits roused.

Although he thought about using the dangers of the Setting Sun Tomb to see if he could break through the bottleneck of the final stage, he would need to make preparations or his life would be in danger.

He first planned on refining two top-grade spirit tools that were to his satisfaction, giving him a greater chance of victory in high battles.

But from what he heard about the Heavenly Origin Martial Equipment, he feared it would be difficult to acquire. He had many spirit stones, but he might not have an opportunity to bid on the items.

It would also attract too much attention to himself. After some further thought, he abandoned the idea of bidding for it and planned on refining his own spirit tools.

Chapter 1300: Ice Arrows, Silver Hand

When Han Li looked at the small beast over a hundred meters away, he let out a deep sigh. He panted for a short moment before his breath returned to normal.

However, his eyes didn’t leave the beast for a moment.

The leopard was the same size as a common cat, but it possessed a shocking speed.

Even Han Li’s Shifting Smoke Steps still paled in speed.

As a result, a few swipes managed to land on his azure robes during the battle, revealing the grey armor and golden flesh underneath.

Not only was the beast’s speed astonishing, but its claws were incredibly sharp as well.

There were varying degrees of scars on his armor. Even his cultivated hardy body had blood drawn from the feline’s claws.

Fortunately, under the effects of various medicines, fruits, and treasures, his flesh had become as hardy as an ordinary magic treasure and possessed shocking regenerative abilities. In a short moment, Han Li was able to heal his wounds.

Even so, Han Li still felt quite gloomy.

When he first encountered the leopard, it appeared soundly sleep on top of a nearby tree and appeared harmless.

At that time, Han Li’s mind welled with a child-like curiosity and thought to pet the small beast.

But he hadn’t expected at all that he would startle the beast and send it flying into a ferocious rage.

In a few leaps, it would surround him with a dozen after images attacking him.

As he was unable to release his spiritual sense, he was unable to grasp its location even with his spirit eyes and suffered much from it.

Eventually, the small beast was forced to retreat with minute scars covering its body.

Helpless, Han Li could only use the Smoke Sifting Steps to its maximum level and circulate the enormous power of his body into his arms, flicking his spear until it became a cloud of black light.

As the spear shadow whistled, it inspired fear in the beast, stalling off its attacks.

But no matter how powerful Han Li may be, he couldn't sustain his attack for long.

As the spear in his hand somewhat slowed, the leopard swept through spear mist and swiped at Han Li’s throat.

In Han Li’s furious alarm, he desperately exerted a speed greater than before and quickly turned the spear to block the leopard’s claw.

The small beast was greatly alarmed and jumped ten meters away. Then it cautiously stared at Han Li with a pair of green eyes.

Han Li and the leopard found themselves in a deadlock.

The beast was extremely gloomy to find a strange character such as Han Li who possessed immense strength and impenetrable flesh.

With the formation of the stalemate, Han Li used this opportunity to thoroughly examine the leopard with narrowed eyes.

Soon, Han Li let out a sigh.

Apart from its small size, it appeared to be an ordinary leopard. After searching through his memories of the records he read in Setting Sun City, he wasn’t able to think of what this ferocious ancient beast could be.

It was also impossible for it to be a demon beast.

This small beast was fighting solely with the strength and abilities of its body. It didn’t possess any demonic power.

This should be a beast variant.

After a long while, that was the only conclusion Han Li could think of.

Eventually, the small beast lost its patience and an ominous light flashed in its eye. It crouched in preparation for another attack.

Han Li’s mind trembled and he tightened his grasp on the spear, assuming a defensive stance.

But white light lit up from his other hand as it grasped a spirit beast pouch.

The pouch contained his myriad of Gold Devouring Beetles.

Han Li made the decision that if the beast pounced on top of him, he would open the bag with his spirit ring.

Although he had no magic power and couldn't control the beetles, he could still rely on its ability to dispose of the small beast. The only trouble would be for him to take them back. Without his spiritual sense, he would have to waste them.

However, Han Li was left with no choice.

The small beast let out a snarl and its body blurred, turning to two, then four...

In the blink of an eye, over thirty identical small beasts appeared on top of the trees with their fangs bared and ready to pounce.

In Han Li’s alarm, he realized that the beast hadn’t made use of its full strength. He immediately brought the back in front of him and was about to toss it.

But then in that crucial moment, a strange bird’s cry sounded from a distance. It sounded like a crow, but it was far harsher.

When the leopard heard this, its face froze and its afterimages disappeared. In the blink of an eye, only one of them remained.

The feline took a deep glance at Han Li before turning its head and shooting deep into the forest.

A short moment later, it disappeared from sight.

Han Li relaxed and retrieved his spirit beast pouch.

Although he didn’t know what was going on, he had no interest in pursuing the cat. He needed to find someplace where he could comprehend what just happened.

In the last battle, there were exceptional developments and he came to a faint realization of something. This was a possibility for him to make a breakthrough.

With a flip of his hand, he took out an azure robe from his storage bracelet and replaced the torn clothes on his body. Then, he head off in a direction away from the leopard.

Because Han Li feared that this feeling of revelation would soon disappear, Han Li didn’t walk far away. Rather, he quickly ran fifty kilometers away to a small valley and struck open a rough cave in a stone wall.

He immediately entered it and sat down cross-legged.

Comprehending his recent flash of enlightenment took him three entire days.

When Han Li opened his eyes once more, he wore a disappointed face.

Although he made some gains from that battle, it wasn’t enough for him to break past his current bottleneck.

But he wasn’t too saddened.

Although he didn’t succeed this time, this illustrated life and death battles would be of great assistance in making a breakthrough. If he experienced several more desperate battles, he was bound to succeed.

After calming his heart, he arranged his belongings and left the cave.

Standing outside the cave, he paused in thought for a long while. He felt that the small beast was the ideal opponent for him. If he could fight it several more times, he may succeed in obtaining an epiphany.

Although he knew it would be dangerous, the restoration of his magic power was far more important.

His expression wavered for a long while before resolving himself to seek out that dangerous leopard.

When he left the valley, Han Li headed in the direction where the leopard is last seen, but he ended up greatly disappointed.

In a single breath, he swept through hundreds of kilometers in the surrounding mountain range, but he found no trace of the beast.

Helpless, Han Li could only depart from the mountains and find another suitable objective.

Over ten days later at the edge of a huge lake, there were a dozen variously dressed body refiners. They were surrounded by crimson snakes with a crest on their heads. The body refiners were using their spirit tools to their utmost extent while attacking the serpents.

The serpent’s attacks were separated into two types. There were those shooting a crimson venom mist, while the others were pouncing at the body refiners like darts.

The venom was tolerable enough as they had swallowed an antivenom beforehand, but they weren’t able to block the serpents’ direct attacks.

The serpents weren’t very large, but their bodies possessed considerable power. Despite the powerful spirit tools the body refiners wielded, they weren’t able to injure the serpents when they struck them.

As a result, the body refiners defended against the serpents many times before they felt their limbs grow heavy and slow.

In addition to these few serpents, there was also a giant serpent behind them.

The serpent appeared to be the group’s king. When it saw that its party had the advantage, it let out several hisses as if it were expressing satisfaction.

But suddenly, booms of lightning sounded from below the lake. Before the humans or the serpents could react, a large silver light flashed from below and countless arrows of light burst forth, felting the humans and serpents on the shore without discrimination.

“AH!” The body refiners could only scream, but they weren’t able to dodge, and the serpents were no better. The lot of them were turned into pincushions by the ice spikes.

Only the huge serpent at the back was quick enough to react. It suddenly bent its body and pounced thirty meters away, narrowly dodging the ice arrows.

But before the serpent landed, the earth beneath it burst. A silver hand shot out from the soil and grabbed the serpent by the neck.

In the serpent’s alarm, it turned like a spring and wound its head around to bite down on the hand.

But a clear ring sounded after the strike. The hand was unharmed and the serpent was in pain, blood trailing from its mouth.

The huge serpent’s teeth were completely shattered by the silver hand’s exceptional hardiness.

In pain, the serpent could only relax its mouth let go.

Another silver hand then strangely appeared nearby. It grabbed ahold of the serpents head and both hands exerted their stretch, pulling them apart. Left headless, the serpent’s body spouted in a fountain of blood.

The serpent corpse was then tossed to the ground.

At that moment, the dust eventually cleared and a silver man appeared, hidden by flickering sliver lights around his body.

At that moment, the ice from the lake moved, suddenly merging into a crystalline person a foot tall. It didn’t have any features of a man or a woman.

“Water Wraith! It’s you!” When the silver silhouette saw the ice woman, he suddenly spoke with a thunderous voice.

The ice person stirred and expressionlessly said, “What? Tie Ren, didn’t you come here to find me? Chi Mie should’ve come too. Call him out.”

“Hehe, there is no need to call for me. I’ll show myself.”

An unfamiliar voice suddenly sounded and a ball of scarlet flame appeared near the silver silhouette. In the blink of an eye, he took the form of a man half a foot tall.

Flames still roiled from his entire body.

Chapter 1320: Fight for the Spirit Land

The fat man let out an inward sigh of relief and thanked the purple-robed man with a smile. He used the jade pendant on a speck of light that said ‘4’.

The number that said ‘4’ was touched by the pendant’s azure light and it blurred to a ‘5’.

This was a location in the Jade Rapid Mountains, the place with the densest spiritual Qi.

When the other sitting cultivators saw this, their expressions vastly changed. A few of the others had a similar idea to him and now had no choice but to take a change of plans.

Because the fat man was a late Deity Transformation-stage cultivator, his cultivation and words seemed to weigh down on the other cultivators.

Now that the fat man had chosen, he returned to his own seat and wanted to see what the others would pick.

Because of his choice, the remaining cultivators eventually stood up to make their choice, both taking an area at Heavenly Sound Mountain, one without any people and one with.

Once those two made their selection, they immediately headed down.

The remaining cultivators each frowned as if unable to come to a decision.

At that moment, Han Li suddenly stood up and walked to the purple-robed man.

The other cultivators were faintly startled.

After all, Han Li had only recently arrived, so it was unexpected for him to quickly come to a decision.

Han Li stroked his storage bracelet and took out a white jade box into his hand. Then with a smile, he handed them to the large purple-robed man with his own jade pendant.

The purple-robed man didn’t immediately take the jade box. Instead, he glanced at Han Li and said, “I heard there was a newly ascended cultivator that arrived in the city. Are you that fellow surnamed Han?”

“Senior is well informed. That is me.” Han Li’s heart trembled, but he showed none of his shock on his face.

“In that case, this should be the first time you’ve picked a cave residence. You won’t need to pay a price and can choose a spirit land.”

“Many thanks, Senior!” Han Li’s face blanked and he quickly withdrew the jade box with a smile.

When the cultivators heard that Han Li was a newly ascended, they glanced at him with an odd expression.

It seemed newly ascended cultivators were a special existence in the city.

The large man quickly examined Han Li’s pendant and gave it back to him with a nod.

Han Li didn’t hesitate and waved his pendant over an uninhabited area.

The azure light passed through it and marked the area with ‘1’.

An uproar was raised when they saw the area Han Li chose.

The area Han Li picked was an area on Jade Rapid Mountain with the most inferior spiritual Qi.

It wasn’t strange for a Deity Transformation-stage cultivator to choose that mountain range, but there were other areas on the mountain range with no one as well. Han Li instead choose the most unremarkable area with the least spiritual Qi. This left them bewildered.

The spirit land’s sole benefit was that to make up for the land’s deficient spiritual Qi, they gave a larger plot of land to make up for it. The land spanned thousands of kilometers, several times in size compared to the other spirit lands on the mountain range.

But everyone knew that the quality of the land was directly related to the amount of spiritual Qi on the land. No matter how wide the land may be, the medicine and ores would certainly be lacking. It is even worse for the cultivator in question.

In the purple-robed man’s surprise, he glanced at the man for a long while and frowned, “You truly chose that as your cave residence. You should know this selection can’t be changed for a hundred years.”

Han Li calmly answered, “I’ve only arrived in the spirit realm. I want to place to stay for the time being, I don’t wish to fight over space with other Fellow Daoists. Although the area is lacking, there is no one else there.”

The purple-robed man then glanced at Han Li with an odd expression and waved his hand. With his originally lazy voice, he said, “If those are your thoughts, then so be it. In any case, after you mark it, no one else will be able to change it.”

Han Li saluted him without further concern and returned to his seat, planning on staying a while longer.

Then, another cultivator stood up and selected the same area as the large purple-robed man.

But then, footsteps clapped and someone entered the second floor unattended by a maid.

When the cultivators on the second floor saw this person, their expressions all changed. The fat man with the largest cultivation, on the other hand, looked at him with bright eyes and he called out, “So it was Fellow Daoist Weng! I didn’t know you were interested in contesting spirit lands!”

The person who entered was a blue-robed man with a headband. He had sharp slanted eyebrows, giving him a menacing impression.

He glanced at the fat man and smiled, “Hehe, If Brother Jin has come to change his cave residence, then so can I.”

This person was a mid-Deity Transformation stage cultivator, but he spoke to the late-stage fat man with a friendly tone. This caused Han Li’s heart to stir and take another look at the blue-robed man.

After all, at this stage of cultivation, every difference in grade signified a vast disparity in power. Of course, those like him that possessed spirit treasures, created heavenly flames from devouring spirits, and practiced heaven-defying abilities like Divine Essensefused Light were the exception.

Since the blue-robed man acted so familiarly with the late-stage cultivator, he should belong in this category.

“Little Brother Weng must be joking. You hold a top grade spirit land. What would you exchange it for.” The fat man stroked his chin and wore a trace of confusion.

“Hehe, I’ve been recently cultivating a secret technique that doesn’t need too much spiritual Qi. I require a larger area, or it will be difficult to cultivate. I'm going to change it for the time being.” The blue-robed man replied with a shock.

“So it was like that,” the fat man said with understanding, but it was unknown if he truly believed him.

When Han Li heard the two talk, he frowned for a brief moment.

The blue-robed man took several steps to the purple-robed man and saluted him, “I pay my respects to Martial Uncle Jiao. My master sends his regards.”

“From that old eccentric’s rotten character, why would he say that? Nevertheless, you master hide from six greater tribulations already. I fear he won’t be able to hide from the seventh, the large man said with a cold laugh.

When the blue-robed man heard the purple-robed man’s reply, he wore an embarrassed expression, but he soon answered, “My master has been secluded for two hundred years. He is preparing to forge a spirit treasure that can withstand the next calamity.”

“A spirit treasure? It seems your master’s luck is quite good. Last time, he had his spirit treasures destroyed to withstand the tribulation and he managed to gather enough materials for another. In that case, your master does have a chance at surviving the next one. Alright, enough of that. I am on duty. Quickly make your choice.” The purple-robed man’s expression sank and he said no further.

“As you wish. The blue-robed man quickly swept his gaze past the man, and looked at several areas with a number and his expression sank.

“Someone actually chose such a remote area on Jade Rapid Mountains.” Not daring to ask the purple-robed man any questions, he turned to the fat man and pointed at an area on the map, “Brother Jin, you’ve been here a while. Do you know who chose that place?”

When the fat man saw where he pointed, an odd expression appeared on his face and he unconsciously glanced in Han Li’s direction.

The blue-robed man quickly understood what the fat man’s face meant. He promptly turned around and closely examined Han Li.

When he saw Han Li’s cultivation was only at early-stage, he wore an arrogant expression and he coldly said, “so you’re the one who chose the spirit land!”

After a moment of silence, Han Li replied, “And you also want it.”

The blue-robed man snorted and eerily said, “My secret technique can only be cultivated in a suitable place. If you’re smart, you’ll renounce your claim. Otherwise, don’t blame me for being ruthless in our fight.” His threat was clear to see.

Han Li remained silent.

In order to avoid a fight, he intentionally picked an area with sparse spiritual Qi. He wanted to avoid provoking any problems as he only had interests in cultivating. He didn’t want to make any enemies that would disturb him.

He completely didn’t expect this plan to backfire and have someone come knocking on his door. Han Li found this matter to be truly laughable.

With blue light shining from his eyes, he took a quick glance at the others.

The large purple-robed man still lazily sat in his seat and had yet to raise his eyes. It appeared he didn’t really care. As for the other cultivators, they looked at him with schadenfreude.

“Senior, if I renounce my choice, will I be able to pick another area.” Han Li calmly asked the purple-robed man.

“You cannot. There are only so many spirit lands. Everyone will only have one opportunity to fight for it. If you lose, you’ll have to contest an empty land in another hundred years.” He replied expressionlessly.

When Han Li heard this, he sighed.

To delay the maturation of his spirit medicines and creation of spirit pills for a hundred years was something he found intolerable.

To the side, the blue-robed man sneered and said, “Even if you have to wait a hundred years, you’ll be able to pick another area. But if you don’t listen to me, hehe...’

When Han Li heard him, he raised his brow and smiled.

“I will not agree to your request. From the way I see it, it’d be best for you to look for a different area to cultivate. I don’t wish to injure you. If I were to make a mistake...”

Han Li spoke casually, and although he only finished half his sentence, his blunt words were extremely obvious.

The spectators were stunned.

Chapter 1321: Unexpected Trouble

Han Li was only at the early-Deity Transformation Stage, and he had been feigning weakness this entire time, so his words naturally came as quite a surprise to everyone.

Even the perpetually expressionless purple-robed man turned to Han Li with a hint of surprise on his face.

A cold light flashed through the eyes of the man with the sharp eyebrows.

"You're a brave one! It's been several hundred years since I've met someone who dared to talk to me like this despite having an inferior cultivation base. In that case, we won't have to hold back in the battle for the Spirit Land in three days," the man said in a menacing voice.

"I'll be sure to take everything you throw at me when the time comes. I'll be taking my leave now." In response, Han Li gave a nonchalant reply before extended a slight bow toward the purple-robed man and departing from the second floor.

The man with the sharp brows looked on at Han Li's departing figure with a dark expression.

...

Not long after that, the fatso and the man with sharp brows appeared in the air high above the Heavenly Jade Pavilion, and the two of them were discussing something through voice transmission.

"Brother Xian, what use do you have for that Spirit Land that you're fighting for? You couldn't disclose this information in there, but you can tell me now, right?" the fatso asked with a benevolent smile.

"I spoke the truth earlier; it is indeed to cultivate a type of secret technique that necessitates a switch of cave abodes. Otherwise, why would I go out of my way to find someplace with such sparse spiritual Qi?" the man with sharp brows replied with a faint sigh.

The fatso chuckled with a disbelieving expression.

The man with sharp brows was quite resigned to see this, and he put on an expression that said "I can't do anything if you don't believe me".

"So be it. Regardless of what objective you have, there must be some circumstances involved that make you unwilling to disclose your goals. Are you really planning not to hold back in the battle against that Han brat?" The fatso suddenly changed the subject.

"Why do you ask? Could it be that you have some ties with him, Fellow Daoist Jin?" The man with sharp brows was rather displeased to hear this question.

"How could I share any ties with him? I just wanted to tell you that he's a cultivator who's only recently ascended to Deep Heaven City," the fatso cautioned.

"A recently ascended cultivator? So what? A new cultivator will ascend to our Deep Heaven City once every two or three years. Do you think I'll lose to an early-Deity Transformation cultivator, Brother Jin? I was wondering why this man dared to be so arrogant; he must've dominated whatever lower realm he came from, and he's taken that cocky demeanor all the way here to the Spirit Realm." The man with sharp brows gave a cold chuckle in response.

"Haha, this man's cultivation base is naturally not noteworthy at all. With your powers, even I wouldn't dare to say that I can defeat you. No matter how powerful an early-Deity Transformation cultivator is, there's no way that he'd be a match for you. However, the ascended cultivators in the city always like to look after one another, so just teach him a lesson and don't actually kill him. Otherwise, even with Senior Ming as a backer, things could become quite troublesome for you if those guys become aware that you killed one of them," the fatso cautioned in a meaningful and heartfelt manner.

"This man has been far too arrogant, so I'll naturally be teaching him a good lesson. As for whether I'll actually be taking his life, we'll see when the battle comes." A cold light flashed through the man's eyes.

"Alright, in that case, I have nothing else to say. In three days, I also have to go and fight those four guys. I don't even know if I'm going to be able to win my own battle." A concerned look appeared on the fatso's face.

"You're being far too modest if you say that, Brother Jin. I heard that Brother Jin recently obtained a primordial treasure that possesses incredible abilities, and it's no less powerful than a spirit treasure." A peculiar smile appeared on the man's face.

The fatso's expression changed upon hearing this before he quickly recomposed himself.

"I didn't think that you’d heard about that already, Brother Weng. Indeed, I did obtain a rather powerful treasure recently, but to say that it's as powerful as a spirit treasure is a bold exaggeration. It simply has some protective properties." The fatso waved his hands in response.

"Oh really?" A hint of a smile appeared on the man's face.

After that, the two of them conversed for a while longer, each of them harboring their own ulterior motives, before the fatso departed as a streak of red light.

The man with the Weng surname looked on with a dark expression and harrumphed coldly.

"Hmph, he's trying to anger me and make me strike up a vendetta against those ascended cultivators. What a devious plan!"

"That man knows a lot about you and is already beginning to suspect you, so you should be more careful from now on. He's not anything to worry about, but his grandfather is someone whom even I'd rather not face." Another man's voice suddenly sounded above him.

Spiritual light then flashed there, and a green jade-like wyrm that was around a foot in length appeared.

The man immediately extended a respectful bow toward the green wyrm as he said, "Don't worry, Master. As soon as I obtain the Spirit Land, I'll completely seal it off immediately. Unless that fatso knows anything concrete, he won't be able to do anything."

"I trust that you'll do a good job. This is quite an important matter and if it weren't for the fact that I'm at a critical juncture in refining my spirit treasure, I definitely wouldn't just be deploying an avatar here. I hope you won't disappoint me." The wyrm nodded in response.

"I'll be sure not to disappoint you, Master," the man vowed before a hesitant look appeared on his face.

"But Master, are we sure that the information we have is accurate? The spiritual Qi there really is quite sparse; it doesn't appear possible that that man would've passed away there."

"Of course we're not completely sure, but with that person's identity, we have to give it a try even if there's only the slightest sliver of a chance. If it's true, then we'll be able to obtain that person's treasures and cultivation arts. In that case, not only would I not have to worry about my upcoming tribulation transcendence, it's quite possible that you'll be able to reach the Spatial Tempering Stage as well. Hence, defeat is not an option for you in three days. If the opponent does indeed prove to be quite troublesome, then there's no need for you to hold back; just kill him on the spot. The aftermath may be a little troublesome, but it's nothing compared to that person's treasures and cultivation arts." The wyrm's voice suddenly cooled significantly.

The man's heart jolted upon hearing this, but he immediately replied, "I understand, Master."

"All ascended cultivators have different tricks up their sleeves, so make sure you don't get complacent. Even though this man is only at the early-Deity Transformation Stage, I'll lend you my Thousand Soul Bell just in case. You'll have three days to refine it, and that should be enough for you to temporarily use the treasure. With that treasure, your victory will be assured." The wyrm opened its mouth after a brief period of contemplation, following which a ball of Yin Qi was expelled from within its body. A black bell that was around an inch in size was enshrouded within the Yin Qi, and there were countless runes visible on the surface of the bell.

The man was ecstatic to hear this, and he hurriedly extended words of gratitude toward the wyrm. He then rustled his sleeve, and a burst of blue light shot forth to accept the bell.

After that, the wyrm gave him a few more instructions before disappearing up his other sleeve.

Only then did the man turn around and fly toward another direction as a streak of blue light.

Han Li was naturally oblivious toward these exchanges, and nor could he have imagined that someone really did intend to kill him.

After departing from the Heavenly Jade Pavilion, he didn't immediately return to the Flying Spirit Palace. Instead, he flew for over half a day according to the annotations on the map, finally settling in the air before looking down at the city in the distance with his brows furrowed in contemplation.

Come to think of it, it was more accurate to call this place the State of Tian Yuan rather than Deep Heaven City. The area governed by this city was comparable to a small state in the human world.

However, the Deep Heaven City wasn't actually all that vast in a strict sense; it was only several tens of thousands of square kilometers in area, and had been sealed off by massive city gates. The city itself was trapezoid in shape with city gates on the front and rear, while the thick mist from massive immortal formations obscured the remaining two sides. Even True Spirit level beings wouldn't be able to barge their way through the mist. The wall that facing the primordial world was the narrowest one at less than 100 kilometers in length, yet the watchtowers that had runes carved into them stretched for several tens of thousands of feet into the sky, striking the onlooker with a sense of awe and fear.

Outside this massive wall, there was a large number of human and demons patrols guarding this area day and night, and all types of restriction formations were also constantly activated.

Within the city wall, there was an army of over 1,000,000 humans and demons that was permanently situated in the city.

Such meticulous defensive measures ensured that Deep Heaven City had never been successfully invaded by foreign races ever since the day of its founding.

In comparison, the city wall on the other side was nowhere near as imposing and well-guarded. However, it stretched for over 500 kilometers, and there were many humans and demons who would access it to enter and exit the three regions and seven territories. Most of these beings were planning to go on adventures in the primordial world while the rest were coming to buy and sell things in Deep Heaven City. As such, the city was an extremely lively and bustling place.

After exiting the boundaries of Deep Heaven City, there was a vast stretch of mountain ranges and the occasional small mortal settlement. However, there was definitely no second cultivator city.

On one hand, these mortal settlements provided some essential supplies for Deep Heaven City and on the other hand, they provided a constant supply of low-grade cultivators and body refinement warriors. Of course, in the areas that had been assigned to the demon race, there were also countless beasts and low-grade demon beasts, thereby providing replenishments to the demons in the city.

The humans and demons were forced to join forces and guard Deep Heaven City together here in this Spirit Realm, but the inevitable truth was that the two races did not see eye to eye. As such, in order to prevent interracial conflict, the entire city was split in half using a massive light barrier, with each race governing one half of the city.

As for the area outside the city, there was also an unnamed no-man's-land acting as the border while each race governed half of that land.

The only place where humans and demons could coexist was the elder tower at the center of the city.

Not only was this tower several times thicker than other massive towers, it was also where the most powerful beings in the city were gathered. Among them, there were a dozen or so Body Integration Stage elders from both races who made decisions on important matters.

As such, this tower appeared extremely mysterious in the eyes of the city's residents.

Chapter 1324: The Might of a Body Refinement Warrior

As soon as the black bell was hurled into the air, it released a string of crisp chimes.

Han Li was suddenly struck by the feeling that a massive boom had erupted within his spiritual sense, following which his body spasmed as if he'd been electrocuted, and he almost plummeted from the sky.

Han Li was naturally shocked by this development, and his Great Development Technique activated of its own accord to send a stream of coolness circulating through his mind.

His face had paled significantly, but his body was finally back to normal.

"That's also a spirit treasure! There's no way that a normal treasure could possess such power!" A hint of wariness flashed through Han Li's heart as he reflexively retaliated.

He made a hand seal, and his spiritual sense converged into a ball in his mind before being expelled toward his opponent.

Meanwhile, Han Li's opponent was even more shocked than he was to see Han Li recover so easily from the effects of the Thousand Soul Bell.

Even though this attack wasn't the bell's most powerful ability, it was very difficult for opponents of a lesser cultivation base to withstand such an attack.

He gritted his teeth, and just as he was about to pour forth even more magic power into the bell, a burst of acute pain suddenly tore through his spiritual sense, as if a sharp spike had been forcibly stabbed into his brain.

Unfortunately for him, his spiritual sense wasn't as powerful as Han Li's. As such, he was quite susceptible to Han Li's Spirit Stun Thorn attack, causing him to let loose a howl of pain as he threw his hands over his head, while his body completely curled up into a ball.

His Nascent Soul also instantly disappeared into his body.

In an instant, he had lost control over the Thousand Soul Bell in the air.

A cold light flashed through Han Li's eyes upon seeing this, and he completely ignored the oncoming giant puppet as he pointed a finger toward the massive golden lotus flower in the distance.

The massive lotus flower immediately rotated rapidly as it came crashing down from above, encapsulating the black bell in a burst of golden light.

Just as the golden lotus flower enshrouded the Thousand Soul Bell, the green puppet had swelled to around 60 to 70 feet in size, raising a massive fist before swinging it violently toward Han Li.

A loud thump erupted as the puppet's punch was kept at bay by the Heavenvoid Cauldron. However, the cauldron tremored violently as it shrank down to around half its size. This puppet possessed extraordinary strength!

Meanwhile, a burst of ghastly howls rang out from within the massive golden lotus flower. A giant bell projection around 10 feet in size appeared at the center of the golden lotus flower, warding off all of the flower's sharp golden petals.

At the same time, wisps of black threads emerged from within the black bell, binding the golden lotus flower, forcibly slowing down its rotation.

Han Li was rather bewildered upon seeing this, yet just as he was about to inject more power into his treasure, the giant black wolf surfaced behind him like a wraith before pouncing toward him from behind.

Its claws were able to pierce through Han Li's grey Divine Essencefused Light barrier without any trouble.

The Divine Essencefused Light was indeed powerful, but its powers were not applicable to existences outside the realm of the five elemental powers.

Just as the giant wolf thought that its sneak attack had succeeded, two shimmering golden fists suddenly hurtled toward its front paws.

Following two resounding booms, its front paws were completely pulverized by the pair of golden fists.

The wolf let loose a howl of anguish as its body shot back from the tremendous resulting force of the clash.

Right at this moment, Han Li finally turned around to face it. His entire body was shimmering with golden light, making it appear as if he were a divine deity forged from gold.

At the sight of the backpedaling black wolf, Han Li wore a cold expression as his body shot forth through the air. A string of afterimages was left in his wake, and he appeared above the wolf's head in the blink of an eye.

After recovering his magic power, Han Li was able to unleash his Shifting Smoke Steps in mid-air.

Even though this technique didn't grant him as much speed as the Thunderstorm Wings and the Nine Gale Transformations, when used in conjunction with Han Li's insanely powerful body, it was very effective for movement over short distances.

Upon seeing Han Li appear above its head, the giant black wolf's feral instincts were set off as it blasted a ball of black light out of its mouth, which was aimed straight at Han Li.

However, Han Li merely waved a casual golden palm through the air, and the black ball of light was swatted flying as if it were a pitiful fly.

At the same time, he injected his magic power into his eyes in a frenzy, following which piercing blue light instantly erupted from his eyes, allowing him to glean the bodily structure of the entire wolf in a split second.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li's body swayed before he appeared in front of the wolf's stomach in a completely expressionless manner.

His hand's shot forth light lightning, grabbing onto the wolf's head and one of its hindlegs respectively, catching the wolf in two vice-like grips that completely immobilized it. He then let loose a loud roar as he brought both arms apart in one violent motion! With Han Li's current unfathomable strength, even a demon beast constructed from metal could be torn apart with ease, let alone a creature manifested from a talisman.

As a result, the giant wolf's massive head was wrenched off its body in one fell swoop. As soon as the wolf was decapitated, brilliant black light erupted from its body, dissipating into bursts of tumbling black mist. However, its head was still very much alive and kicking, even while it was still clamped within Han Li's golden grasp.

Han Li chuckled coldly as he grabbed the air with his other hand, following which a ball of silver flames emerged.

The ball of fire transformed into a Fire Raven in a flash, and the latter swooped down toward the black wolf's head following a crisp cry.

Amid a howl of shock and horror, silver flames instantly engulfed the wolf's head, reducing it to a ball of black mist in the blink of an eye.

Immediately thereafter, the silver flames completely devoured all of this black mist before reverting back to its Fire Raven form.

The bird opened its mouth to expel a silver talisman, which Han Li rapidly grabbed ahold of.

This talisman was none other than the one that his opponent had summoned earlier, but the light shimmering on its surface had dimmed significantly, indicating that it had expended most of its power.

Meanwhile, the Fire Raven was blasting silver flames out of its mouth, circling around Han Li in an excited manner.

Han Li then turned toward the green giant puppet over 100 feet away before appearing above its head in a flash.

The puppet had been impeded by the Heavenvoid Cauldron, and was ramming its fists into the latter over and over again.

The cauldron was knocked back around 10 feet and shrank with every single punch, but it was able to withstand an attack from the avatar of an elder demon in the past, so it certainly wasn't an easy obstacle to get around. After each successive punch, it would simply return to its original spot and expand once again to its former size, thereby repeating the process over and over again...

The puppet had no intelligence to speak of, and Han Li's opponent was still reeling from the excruciating pain inflicted by the Spirit Stun Thorn. As such, he couldn't manipulate the puppet and it could only attack the giant cauldron with brute force, seeing as it wasn't capable of formulating any superior strategies.

Han Li wasn't very familiar with the puppetry techniques of the Spirit Realm, but the puppetry techniques in the Great Development Treasured Scriptures left behind by the Monarch of Soul Divergence were among the best that could be found in the human world.

As such, despite this giant green puppet’s obvious power, Han Li was able to immediately identify its weakness with his spirit eyes.

He quickly stowed away the silver talisman in his hand before stepping forward. Golden light flashed, and he appeared almost instantaneously behind the massive puppet.

A string of crackles and pops rang out from Han Li's body as he aimed vicious punch toward a certain spot right under the puppet's ribs.

Prior to even making contact with the puppet, his shimmering golden fist was sweeping up immensely powerful winds that threatened to tear through space.

An earthshattering boom erupted as a massive fist indentation that was several inches deep appeared on the puppet's body right under its ribs. It was swept off its feet by the enormous force of Han Li's strike before thudding to the ground.

However, Han Li refused to release the pressure as his fists rained down like a torrential storm on the exact same spot on the puppet's body.

In the blink of an eye, a hole had been punctured into the puppet's body.

Han Li immediately withdrew his fists before rubbing his hands together, sending an arc of golden lightning hurtling directly into the puppet's body through that hole.

A series of explosions rang out from within the puppet's body, following which it began to shrink drastically amid a burst of brilliant green light. In the blink of an eye, it had shrunk down to only around a foot in size before laying on the ground in a completely stationary manner.

It appeared that a complex series of procedures had been undertaken to defeat the black wolf and the green puppet, but it had actually only taken Han Li the span of a few breaths.

At this moment, his opponent finally recovered from the effects of the Spirit Stun Thorn, just in time to witness Han Li destroying his puppet while scintillating golden light radiated from his body.

"Complete mastery of the Vajra Arts! You're a top-grade body refinement warrior as well!" he exclaimed with incredulity etched on his face.

The armor-clad cultivator outside the barrier of light didn't say anything, but he was clearly also quite astonished by what he was witnessing.

Han Li turned to his opponent with a calm expression, and asked, "Would you like to continue, Fellow Daoist Weng?"

The man's expression immediately darkened upon hearing this."Your abilities are indeed far superior to what I'd anticipated, but do you really think that you've won? Even if I have to sacrifice the fruits of over a century of arduous cultivation, I'm going to show you the full power of this Thousand Soul Bell!" Han Li's opponent flew into a thunderous rage as he looked up at the black bell, which was currently grappling with a giant golden lotus flower.

He then began to chant something, and blue light flashed above his head as his Nascent Soul emerged again.

The Nascent Soul wore a grave expression as it made a hand seal with one hand while raising its other hand into the air. A blue pillar of light shot forth, striking the black bell with unerring accuracy as the Nascent Soul began to chant an unintelligible incantation.

The black bell shuddered before absorbing the blue pillar of light as specks of spiritual light.

Taking advantage of this opportunity, the man pointed a finger at the black bell from afar, and it gave off a crisp tinkle.

A burst of violent spatial fluctuations abruptly erupted from within the light barrier, following which a thin black rift appeared in the air above without any warning .

Chapter 1330: Floating Dawn Swamp

"You have a sharp discerning eye, Senior Han. Unfortunately, I've been stuck at this cultivation base for several hundred years already. I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to take that final step before my lifespan runs out," the Daoist priest replied with a wry smile.

Han Li gave him a faint smile in response, and didn't say anything. He pulled the red jade slip off the small golden sword before examining its contents with his spiritual sense.

The other three cultivators waited patiently off to the side.

Moments later, Han Li withdrew his spiritual sense from the jade slip and uttered the name of a place.

"Floating Dawn Swamp!"

"What? How could it be that place?!" Zhuo Chong exclaimed upon hearing this. Dongguo Feng and the Daoist priest were also shocked by this development.

"Why? Is there something wrong with that place?" Han Li asked with furrowed brows.

"That's an understatement! That place is regularly frequented by beings of other races, and many of our fellow Daoists perish there every year! It's an extremely perilous place," Zhuo Chong explained in a grim voice.

"And we'll be the only squad patrolling this place?" Han Li asked with a hint of surprise on his face.

"That most likely won't be the case. The Floating Dawn Swamp is an extremely massive place; even if we fly non-stop, it'll still take us half a month to fly a lap around it. Generally speaking, there would be four or five squads patrolling the place at once," Daoist Priest Ma explained.

"If we're not the only squad there, then we have nothing to complain about. We'll just need to take extra care," Han Li said in an indifferent voice.

"Senior Han, you won't be aware of this, but two years ago, Leader Xuan Guang of the 12th squad was attacked by Shadow Tribe beings in the Floating Dawn Swamp, and he perished on the scene along with two of his companions; Senior Xuan Guang was already a mid-Deity Transformation cultivator at he time!" Dongguo Feng explained with a fearful expression.

"Is that so?" Han Li's expression finally changed slightly upon hearing this.

Right at this moment, the sound of footsteps rang out from the passageways on either side of the hall as a few more people emerged.

Among them were five men and a woman, two of which were elderly men, two of which appeared to be a middle-aged couple, and the remaining two were a young man who appeared to be in his late teens, as well as a boisterous-looking burly man.

These were clearly the squad members who had been meditating in the silent cultivation chambers, and they had emerged clearly because they had somehow been alerted to the arrival of the messenger sword.

All of them were naturally rather surprised to see Han Li before extending respectful bows toward him following introductions made by Zhuo Chong.

Han Li naturally responded politely in kind.

After sweeping his spiritual sense through these squad members, he took an extra glance at the teenager, who introduced himself as bearing the Ying surname.

This was at the pinnacle of the late-Nascent Soul Stage, just like Daoist Priest Ma and Zhuo Chong.

Surprisingly, the two with the lowest cultivation bases were the pair of elderly men.

After learning of the fact that they were being deployed to patrol the Floating Dawn Swamp, all of them also became quite concerned.

"Alright, we can't change the orders issues by our higher-ups, so we'll just have to be more careful in the next few years. Let's set off tomorrow; make sure you're all prepared for our journey by then." Han Li issued a few instructions before making his way into one of the passageways.

He then found a silent cultivation chamber for himself and settled in there. Han Li's nonchalant reaction made all of the cultivators present even more concerned. Everyone turned to Zhuo Chong in the end.

The young man who appeared to be in his teens asked, "Brother Zhuo, did you inform Senior Han of the perils of the Floating Dawn Swamp?"

"Of course I did, but it appears that he hasn't really taken me seriously." Zhuo Chong heaved a faint sigh.

"We have no choice in the matter anyway. The order was issued by the panel of elders; what are we going to do? Resist the orders?" the woman among them said in a resigned voice.

"Obviously we can't resist the order, but we have to at least alert Senior Han to the perils of the swamp so he can treat the situation with more caution. If we really encounter those powerful beings from foreign races, we have to at least be prepared," Daoist Priest Ma said with a concerned stroke of his beard.

Zhuo Chong was silent for a moment before saying, "There's no need to be overly concerned, everyone. The Floating Dawn Swamp is indeed quite a perilous place, but truly powerful beings from foreign races are still quite rare there. On top of that, due to how dangerous the swamp is, we'll receive a handsome reward for our efforts, and we'll be able to take a long rest after this patrol mission. As long as we can survive these next few years, we'll most likely be assigned to less dangerous areas thereafter. You've all heard what Senior Han said; go back and make preparations for our journey tomorrow."

No one else had anything meaningful to contribute to the discussion, so they could only depart amid a rather gloomy atmosphere.

At this moment, Han Li was seated with his legs crossed within the silent cultivation chamber, and there was faint golden light shimmering all over his body. He appeared to be in deep meditation, but there were golden halos flashing erratically behind his head, creating a rather bizarre sight to behold.

A day passed by in the blink of an eye.

When Han Li opened his eyes again and emerged from the silent cultivation chamber, Zhuo Chong and everyone else was already waiting there for him. All of them immediately rose to their feet and extended respectful salutes at the sight of Han Li.

Han Li waved a hand before turning his gaze toward a beautiful female cultivator.

This woman appeared to be in her twenties, and her pristine fair skin was almost translucent. Her eyes were shimmering like a pair of bright stars, and Han Li was struck by a sense of familiarity when he looked at her, as if he had seen her somewhere before.

A hint of surprise flashed through Han Li's eyes upon making this observation.

"Senior Han, this is Fairy Xu; she's the direct lineal descendant of an ascended cultivator," Daoist Priest Ma introduced with a smile.

Han Li's heart stirred upon hearing this, but he merely nodded with a calm expression.

The female cultivator also seemed to have a rather cold and aloof personality, and she only extended a clipped greeting toward Han Li before falling silent.

"If everyone's here, then let's set off."

Han Li didn't delay any longer as he led everyone out of the hall, heading directly toward a teleportation stone hall nearby.

This hall was guarded by another group of cultivators, and there was a golden ark situated within the hall, but there was no need to make use of that treasure seeing as the teleportation was only going to be over a relatively short distance.

After handing over his identification badge for examination, their squad split up into groups of three or four to be teleported in separate bouts.

Amid three successive flashes of white light, all 11 members of the squad were teleported out of Deep Heaven City and appeared in an unfamiliar place. After shaking off the rush of dizziness from teleportation, Han Li inspected his surroundings, and his brows furrowed slightly.

They were situated within a small stone chamber with a one-way teleportation formation underfoot. There were all types runes carved into the walls, all of which were flickering and seemed to have been enshrouded under a restriction.

Daoist Priest Ma and the other cultivators that had been teleported to this place in advance were waiting for them outside of the formation.

Han Li made his way out of the teleportation formation in an unhurried manner before striding toward the door of the stone chamber. He then pulled out his azure jade pendant and waved it at the door.

A burst of azure light immediately shot forth, and the runes on the door flickered before it was slowly opened, revealing a passageway leading upward that was around 10 feet wide.

Han Li immediately shot forth into the passageway as a streak of azure light.

His 10 subordinates also hurriedly unleashed their movement techniques in pursuit. Not long after the final person left the stone chamber, spiritual light flashed from the door, and it slowly sealed shut again. Meanwhile, Han Li had already emerged from the passageway and was standing in the air above a small mountain, surveying his surroundings from his vantage point up above.

They were currently situated within a set of bleak and barren mountain ranges. Around 50 kilometers behind them, a vast expanse of white light could be seen, beyond which lay a massive city wall. Even from such a long distance away, everyone could still see the astonishing spiritual light flashing from the runes on the city wall.

Han Li appraised the city wall for a long time with a contemplative look on his face.

As far as he was aware, the wall of Deep Heaven City that was facing the primordial world had no gate. Any humans or demons wishing to access the city from this side had to do so through the teleportation formations within the city.

With this arrangement, the restrictions placed on the city wall would prevent beings of foreign races from being able to infiltrate the city.

However, Han Li wasn't interested in that. Instead, he turned his attention toward another direction.

There, he was greeted by the sight of a string of lush mountains, all of different sizes. A scene of peacefulness and tranquility was portrayed, making it quite difficult to believe that the place was situated within the primordial world.

According to the map, the so-called Floating Dawn Swamp was around 5,000 kilometers away from this place. Due to the special terrain there, cultivators' spiritual sense were impaired, which made it the perfect place for spies from foreign races to survey Deep Heaven City from afar.

As such, Deep Heaven City had no choice but to deploy groups of cultivators to regularly patrol the area. However, all of the spies from the foreign races were quite powerful and were especially proficient in concealment techniques. As such, many humans regularly fell prey to these beings and perished within the swamp.

This was why it was regarded as one of the most dangerous areas to be assigned for patrol duties, and all cultivators on patrol duty prayed that they weren't assigned to this accursed place.

However, Han Li had been deployed to this area, so he had to take extra care during the next few years.

With that in mind, he glanced at the group of cultivators behind him as he instructed, "Let's go."

Thus, their squad of 11 flew into the distance as streaks of light.

A distance of just over 5,000 kilometers was certainly not difficult to cover for a group of cultivators at or above the Nascent Soul Stage. As such, it didn't take long before Han Li caught sight of their destination in the distance.

A turbulent green light appeared in his field of vision first.

After drawing closer, Han Li managed to identify that this was not some green line; it was instead a vast expanse of murky mist.

He slowed down slightly as he flipped over a hand, upon which a special formation plate appeared over his palm.

Han Li pointed a finger at the formation plate, and a layer of red light immediately lit up over its surface. At this moment, all of the cultivators behind him also brought out identical formation plates and did the same thing.

These formation plates were known as Foreign Spirit Plates, and were treasures assigned to all cultivators from Deep Heaven City on patrol duty. The treasure could allow them to detect the presence of beings from foreign races within a certain distance.

The limitation of this plate was that its detection effect was only applicable toward a single direction, but with so many plates summoned at once, all of which were focusing on different directions, they proved to be quite useful.

Thus, Han Li and his group carried the formation plates in their hands as they slowed down and carefully ventured into the mist.

Soon, all of them had disappeared.

Chapter 1335: Lightning Turned Wood

Han Li curiously examined the items on display and swept his spiritual sense past them.

The branch had extremely thin wood spiritual Qi, but it also possessed an intense lightning-attributed power as if it was formed from lightning. He was astonished by its existence.

This immediately reminded him of the Heaven Lightning Bamboo.

But even ten-thousand-year-old Golden Lightning Bamboo didn’t possess such fearsome lightning power. Its Divine Devilbane Lightning is usually well restrained.

As for the crimson gem, it let out a fishy scent as if it were the inner core of a beast, but he couldn't tell its origins.

Han Li looked at this with some interest, but after a moment more, he quietly left to another vendor’s booth.

He then arrived at demon vendor with head-sized chunks of black ore that gave off a chill.

...

Han Li slowly paced through the hall and looked at what was on display. He would occasionally stop and take a close look.

From start to finish, he hadn’t said a word as if he were ignoring the vendors entirely.

Han Li quickly looked through all the items on display, but he found himself somewhat disappointed.

Although all the items were rare enough, there was nothing that truly tempted him.

Although these items have come from the wilderness, there were unfamiliar items and would only be useful to an odd few.

Han Li swept his gaze around. Just as he thought about whether he should leave the hall, he suddenly heard footsteps behind him.

The white mist around him blurred and he suddenly turned around. The footsteps then came to a stop as if in surprise of Han Li’s quick reaction.

The person was a demon cultivator as they were covered in black Qi. They had a slim body and was examining Han Li.

They were both hidden by secret techniques. Apart from a faint silhouette, nothing could be made out.

“Is there anything you want from me?” Han Li calmly asked.

“Did you not find any suitable items, Fellow Daoist?” A pleasant female voice spoke from the black cloud.

“Yes, I haven’t found anything that caught my interest. Why did you ask me that?”

“It appears this is your first time at the Profound Zenith Hall. In truth, apart from what is put on display the truly good items are found in private exchanges,” the woman calmly said.

“So it was like that. But wouldn’t it be easier to find a suitable customer if one showed it in the open?” Han Li said with a frown.

“So you don’t know, Fellow Daoist, or you’re being deliberately dense. Even with the concealment pendants and banners, it is still easy to tell one apart. Furthermore, some items are quite provocative so it isn’t best to have too many people know about it. Alright, that’s enough for now. Do you have any items you wish to trade?” The woman’s impatience seemed to grow colder out of impatience.

“So long as you have good items, I am willing to trade. However, I must ask why did you seek me out.” Han Li said.

“It’s rather simple,” the woman said with an indifferent tone, “I was able to tell that you were most likely someone new to Deep Heaven City when you were closely examining the vendor items. Although our cultivation is restricted, I can tell on closer inspection that you are most likely a Deity Transformation-stage cultivator. You are a suitable person to trade with me, and you weren’t the first person that I sought out. Tell me what you have that is suitable for a demon. Apart from a few of my own items, I’ve also been entrusted to several items by my comrades. That’s why you take out all your good things.”

When Han Li heard this, he smiled.

“I do have a few things that are suitable for demons. But can I take a look at your things first?”

“Hmph,” the woman coldly chuckled, “I have spirit medicines, materials, a few human magic treasures and ancient treasures. What do you want?”

Han Li’s eyes wandered for a bit and he asked, “I don’t need any finished goods, but I am interested in materials. Do you have any True Toad spirit blood? I require it.”

The woman paused and immediately shook her head, “True Toad spirit blood. Hehe, you sure know how to pick them. True Toad Liquid is not only useful to humans but demons as well. No one would be selling it in the Profound Zenith Hall .”

“If that’s the case, then do you have any five-thousand-year-old gold grass and...” Han Li didn’t pay any mind to the woman’s mocking tone and promptly listed other materials that he lacked from his pill formulas.

When she heard Han Li, her face turned unsightly. When Han Li was finished, she gloomily said, “Don’t delude yourself. Those materials are for cultivation progression pills. They are all found in the wilderness, so our demon clan is lacking them as well. We definitely wouldn’t be trading those to humans.”

Han Li wasn’t disappointed by her words and calmly proposed, “There is no need to be anxious. I don’t even need the right year of the herbs. Saplings and seeds will do as well. I am even willing to trade at cost.”

After some hesitation, the woman said with a doubtful tone, “In that case, it could be possible, but it is also troublesome as I don’t have any of those right now. Let me see what you have.”

“So long as you can gather them together, I will trade with you the next time I am here.” Han Li said with a happy tone.

“Yes, but this is something that I must take a look at first. Even if seeds and saplings are commonly scarce when few people wish to buy them. But in case I do find them, what will you be giving to me? I won’t be considering spirit stones, even high-grade ones.” The woman said with an arrogant tone.

When Han Li heard this, he sent her a voice transmission with a calm expression.

“What? You actually have ten-thousand-year-old spirit herbs?” The woman trembled inside the fog and she spoke with delight.

Han Li smiled and said, “So long as you can find the items I require, I will give them to you.”

After her delight passed, doubts filled her mind. “Why don’t you make medicine pills with those herbs? Why do you want to trade with me?”

“Please don’t ask too much about my circumstances. If you feel that it is suitable, please do your utmost to gather those materials. The next time I come here, I will trade with you. Consider this one to be a down payment.” Han Li soon swiped his hand over his storage bracelet and took out a half-foot-long wooden case and casually handed it over to her.

The woman in the black Qi was startled and unconsciously reached out for it. Her expression wavered and she quickly brushed her spiritual sense past the gap in the wooden box.

She yelped and took a long look at the item in the box. Then she slowly opened the lid and her expression turned solemn.

“Are you truly planning to use this as a down payment. Don’t you fear that I will take it and won’t return?” The woman coldly said.

“This is a trifling three thousand year old herb. With your status, you aren’t going to do something like that. Additionally, this is a display of sincerity to guarantee your business. So long as you bring those medicine herbs to me, I’ll definitely leave you satisfied.” He said with a neutral tone.

She flipped her hand and put away the box. Then, she confidently said, “It seems you are sincere about the deal, but items you want can’t be gathered in a short amount of time. I will need several years to gather the three medicines.”

“Good, I await good news.” Pleased, Han Li saluted her.

To him, a medicine herb of several thousand years wasn’t valuable. It was a cheap price to gain her trust. Furthermore, Han Li was confident that his promise of a ten-thousand-year-old medicine herb was enough to have her find his items.

Since Han Li was unwilling to attract too much attention to the human side of the city, this was a suitable method.

The woman nodded and wordlessly left.

Han Li narrowed his eyes to look at the slender silhouette through the black mist. Suddenly, he began to walk to the exit on the human side.

But when he walked past the first human vendor, his eyes were drawn onto the branch once more and he unconsciously stopped. After some hesitation, he walked over.

“Could you tell me about the origins of this item?” Han Li walked over to the vendor and reached out for the green branch. He then stroked it with his finger.

“The origin? I saw heavenly lightning strike dried spirit wood. Afterwards, it grew alive and turned into this spirit wood. I don't know anything about its origins or usage.” A hoarse, aged voice spoke from the white mist.

Han Li flipped the branch several times and muttered, “Heavenly lightning turned wood. How surprising.”

“Hehe, rare indeed,” the old man chuckled, “However, I won’t hide this from you. This item contains potent lightning power. Even if you forcefully refine it, you won’t be able to use it for tool refinement. I wanted to see if the demons were interested, but it seems you are too!”

Chapter 1338: Soul Freezing into the Body

Under the gaze of so many people, Fairy Xu felt apprehension, nevertheless, she waved her sleeve and summoned a white light. It circled above her to reveal a crystalline flying sword.

It was her bonded magic treasure, the Ice Crystal Sword!

To tell the truth, she felt largely helpless.

Even if a trick was done to the Green Wave Sword, she was only given a little bit of time to refine the Myriad Year Profound Jade that was given to her into the sword. However, this still greatly increased the sword strength, so there was a chance to seal the blade in ice.

Although she released her sword, she didn’t dare to immediately attack the green sword. Instead, she hesitantly glanced at Han Li.

Han Li took a glance at both of the flying swords and he reached out to one of the swords.

Fairy Xu felt her sword largely tremble. Then, it flew against her control and arrived in Han Li’s hand.

He grabbed the sword’s hilt and flicked his finger against its body, emitting a phoenix’s cry.

The sound was extremely pleasant, a near heavenly tone.

The old man couldn't help but sneer.

Although cultivators of their level could use secret techniques to forcefully boost the might of their magic treasures, it was a difficult task to do this to another treasure.

After all, regardless of the nature of the spiritual power and technique will conflict and make it difficult to fuse together.

When he forcefully boosted the power of his disciple’s magic treasure, he unexpectedly acquired an extremely profound spirit talisman. After spending half a month refining it, it finally became this powerful.

As Han Li was only an early Deity Transformation cultivator, he didn’t believe that he could exceed that power in only an instant.

Furthermore, sealing the Green Wave Sword in ice was something that only equivalent ice-attributed power could perform. This in itself was a huge restriction.

As this quickly flashed through the old man’s mind, he had no fear of Han Li’s action.

“A good sword!” As if having seen through the old man’s thoughts, the corner of Han Li’s lip twitched and a silver flame burst out from the hilt of the sword. In the blink of an eye, it wrapped around the sword and disappeared into it.

The crystalline sword turned silver-white in the blink of an eye. The design of a sailing flame bird now appeared on its surface, lifelike in detail as if it had been carved there from the very beginning.

Han Li had forcefully injected his Spirit Engulfing Flame into the Ice Crystal Sword, inducing this bizarre transformation.

The Spirit Engulfing Flame was an inconceivable ability that devoured spiritual power. As it was formed from Great Yin Trueflame and Puresun Flame Essence, it could shift between extreme cold and heat, allowing it to fuse into the flying sword with ease.

The old man’s eyes widened for a moment and then narrowed his eyes. As for the others, they were greatly shocked.

Then in a gust of wind, Han Li tossed the flying sword back into the air.

Fairy Xu quickly cast a spell seal at it with joy on her face and quickly regained control. Afterwards, she chanted an incantation and flicked her fingers, striking the sword one after another, completely filling the sword with the entirety of her magic power.

Afterwards, the flying sword let out a series of drones and trembled. A layer of silver flames appeared on its surface and wrapped around it, instantly transforming it into a three-meter-long silver flame bird.

The temperature in the entire hall steeply dropped as soon as the flame bird appeared. Even a layer of white shining frost began to appear on the ground.

Fairy Xu let out a delicate shout and the flame bird wildly flapped its wings, changing into the green flying sword.

Seeing that the ice sword was greatly empowered by Han Li, the dwarf let out a trace of terror and could only grit his teeth, casting a spell seal and commanding his own magic treasure.

The green sword blurred as light brightly shined from it. It took the form of a horned green wyrm and fiercely charged forward.

A loud explosion shook the air.

The green wyrm and the silver flame bird collided, weaving green light and silver flames together. The bird then opened its mouth and bit off half of the flood dragon’s body, devouring it without a trace.

The dwarf loudly shouted and spat out a glob of blood. He was stupefied in fear.

A loud bang sounded from the flame bird and turned into a silver ice mist, covering the damaged green wyrm entirely.

Under the glow of silver light, a loud crack sounded. A thirty-meter-tall boulder of ice appeared in the air.

The flood dragon let out a wail inside the ice and it disappeared, only leaving behind a flying sword that dimly shined.

Unnoticed by everyone, a thin thread of silver light shot out of the mist when the Green Wave Blade revealed itself and silently vanished inside of it.

A strange scene occurred.

The dwarf was clearly sixty meters away from his magic treasure, but at the same time his blade was frozen, his body collapsed onto the floor as if he fainted.

This was a heaven-defying ability of the Spirit Engulfing Flame.

Even Spatial Tempering cultivators couldn't guard against this ability, let alone the magic treasure of a Nascent Soul cultivator. Even if it was strengthened, it collapsed in a single strike.

When Fairy Xu saw this, she quickly waved her hand in delight.

The silver ice mist condensed back into a silver flying sword and returned to her.

Along the way, a ball of silver flame left the sword and shot back towards Han Li, soon to disappear into his body.

Meanwhile, the old man Huang Bao recovered from his shock and his body in his rage. He soon appeared at his disciple’s side and he quickly discovered a layer of frost on the dwarf’s body. His face was blue as if he died from frostbite.

“A frozen soul in his body!” When Huang Bao saw this, he wore a face of shock.

Nevertheless, he was still a Deity Transformation-stage cultivator. He instantly waved his sleeve at the huge boulder of ice and released a streak of red light.

Bang. The light quickly coiled around the boulder and a cloud of flame entered the ice.

The temperature in the hall sharply rose and the ice was thawed in an instant and the green flying sword recovered its freedom. It immediately returned into the dwarf’s body.

Han Li looked on with an indifferent expression.

To conceal the true abilities of the Spirit Engulfing Flames, he reduced its power and had the Ice Crystal Sword itself freeze over the blade. Otherwise, with its abilities as a Heavenly Flame, the ice it left behind wouldn’t have been easily thawed. However, he did display a bit of might to make sure they knew better than to bother him.

He previously commanded a trace of the Spirit Engulfing Flames’s extreme cold and had it enter the flying sword. Through the dwarf’s mental connection, he had it invade the dwarf’s body.

This ability to freeze the soul and affect the body was an ability he had only been able to use recently.

He also researched related information about this once before. This ability was quite powerful and could only be achieved by a few legendary glacial flames.

As such, it was truly quite effective.

Han Li became an enigmatic figure in the old man’s eyes.

The old man quickly took out a fire-red medicine pill and placed it in the dwarf’s mouth. He saw the blue color on his face quickly fade away and he let out a breath before looking at Han Li with a wavering expression.

Having thought to himself for a moment, the old man eventually saluted Han Li with a forced smile and said, “Brother Han’s abilities are quite fearsome. It is my loss. My disciple will drop the matter of marriage. I will bid farewell.”

He then brought the dwarf out from the hall.

Han Li returned the salute, but he said nothing else. When he saw all trace of the old man leave, his expression sank. Before Fairy Xu could utter her thanks, he coldly asked, “Who is that man?”

Fairy Xu was startled. Before she knew the meaning of Han Li’s words, the green-eyed man hurriedly explained, “Don’t worry, Senior Han. Huang Bao and his disciple comes from a small sect known as Quicksand Valley. It isn’t some ancient sect. Huang Bao himself is the sect’s greatest cultivator.

“So it was like that. I don’t have to worry about any further troubles!” Han Li then turned to her and said, “Fellow Daoist Xu, this will be the only time I go out of my way to help you. If something else comes to trouble you, you’d best fend for yourself!”

Fairy Xu’s heart sank, and she respectfully answered, “This Junior understands. Many thanks for your help, Senior. I definitely won’t trouble you in the future.”

Han Li nodded and then walked out of the hall in bold steps before taking off.

When the green-eyed man saw Han Li left, he wryly laughed and said, “That silver flame actually possessed the power of extreme cold and was able to freeze the soul and enter the body. But it doesn’t match the glacial flames of legend. Fellow Daoist Xu, Senior Han seems to look after you. Do you know what flame it is?”

Fairy Xu let out a sigh and said, “Senior Han has a faint relation to my ancestor, but this is the first time I’ve heard of this glacial flame. On the patrol, he engulfed an entire fused beastman with that flame. Having that ability isn’t so strange, but it seems that he isn’t fond of others hearing about him. Brother Zhuo had best keep quiet about this, or else...”

When he heard this, his expression changed and he nodded in agreement.

During that time, Han Li was flying towards the market in an azure streak.

According to his information, the auction should begin at noon. It would be at the time he arrived.

Chapter 1339: Surprise at the Auction

When Han Li arrived, it was nearing noon. In just a moment, he used a secret technique to transform himself into a large man with long facial hair and entered the Profound Zenith Hall.

The people at the entrance were already exchanging spirit stones for concealment pendants to enter the hall.

All of them were at Deity Transformation-stage and above.

Han Li even spotted three Spatial Tempering cultivators entering.

After some thought, he also walked in and gave the guard a pouch filled with spirit stones. The guard swept his spiritual sense past it and nodded, handing him a jade pendant and opened the way for him. He promptly said, “After you enter, head left.”

When Han Li heard this, he was stunned and he hesitantly walked in.

After they entered the passage, he astonishedly discovered that the straight passage he originally took was now exceptionally twisted and split down the middle.

It was like the Profound Zenith Hall was completely different.

It seemed the restrictions in the hall had changed as well.

Nevertheless, Han Li did as the guard advised and headed down the left side.

Soon, he entered the dark passage and vanished.

After the time it took to finish a meal, he found himself in a pitch-black stone room.

The room was three meters wide with walls to all sides apart from a spacious opening. There were a jade table, a bamboo chair and a table with a red spell plate.

There were many of these stone rooms densely packed spread across three hundred meters in the air. They were flying stone rooms.

The entire hall was three thousand meters wide and nearly had a thousand stone rooms floating above it.

Faint azure talisman characters glowed from the surface of the stone room. Each room had a considerable distance between the two as if they were floating lamps.

Han Li sat down in the chair, looked down at the auction below and clicked his tongue.

In the instant he entered the large hall, he entered an odd spell formation and teleported to the room. Under his examination, he discovered the room wasn’t only suspended in air, but it also blocked spiritual sense. With the addition of the light pendant concealing them, it would guarantee the anonymity of the bidders.

It appeared the master of the auction knew that cultivators feared arousing envy and spent much time on how to solve this.

Han Li leaned back in his chair and rested his eyes for a short time. Soon, another several hundred cultivators entered the hall, nearly filling it to its brim.

Han Li widely opened his eyes and took a breath.

When one normally entered the auction, they needed to be at Deity Transformation-stage at the very least. But this small auction managed to gather nearly a thousand Deity Transformation cultivators.

This was something that couldn't even be imagined in the mortal realm.

However, this was also impossible to happen unless it occurred in the other cultivator cities in the three human regions, barring Deep Heaven City.

Suddenly, melodic rings rang through the hall. The hall’s open gates slow closed with a creak and a clack.

The dim hall now became completely dark.

Immediately, several head-sized moonlight stones appeared above the auction. The appearance of their soft white light caused the cultivators to unconsciously looked down.

On a thirty-meter-tall platform, a spell formation suddenly appeared, followed by a flash of white light. A white-robed old man made an appearance.

As soon as he appeared, the cultivators became restless. A few even uttered the old man’s name in shock.

“Grandmaster Chi!”

“Why would he appear here? Could it be the auction...”

...

Whispers continued to echo through the hall.

When Han Li heard the disturbance, his heart stirred and he curiously examined the old man.

He only possessed mid Deity Transformation cultivators, but his headful of silver hair and his friendly face gave him a bearing expected of a dignified cultivator. When he heard others address him as grandmaster, he reckoned the title should come from astonishing attainments in either pill refinement or some other art.

The white-robed old man coughed and spoke with a gentle voice, “It seems I don’t need to introduce myself to you. Many of you do recognize me. Normally, I wouldn’t appear at such an event, but this auction has things that I’ve personally appraised. Furthermore, I am greatly interested in these items and took the initiative to act as the auction host. It appears that none of you have any objections!”

“Chi Lao must be joking. Having a tool refinement master to host the auction is exactly what we would want!”

“Not bad, not bad! Brother Chi’s personal appraisal can’t be wrong. We’ll be more at ease.”

...

Praise repeatedly sounded through the floating rooms.

Although many of the cultivators didn’t say anything, they also raised no opposition. It appeared that the white-robed old man was quite famous.

The old man continued, “In order for everyone to know what’s going on, I’ll give you a preview of what to expect. There will be three items of extraordinary value. They were rarely seen in the last several hundred years. Among them are top quality items from the wilderness, and a spirit treasure that has rose up to the primal myriad spirit rankings. As for the last item, it is an entire set of cultivation arts that was left behind by a late-stage Body Integration Senior that shook the worlds of both humans and demons.”

The cultivators were greatly alarmed as if they couldn't believe what they just heard. The entire hall was filled with silence.

The item from the wilderness wasn’t much as it was unknown, but a spirit treasure on the primal spirit rankings and the primary cultivation art of a Body Integration stage cultivator were incredibly rare treasures. If any of those items appeared on the outside, it would provoke a massacre.

As the hearts of these cultivators heavily thumped, the atmosphere became extremely grave.

“Brother Chi, since there are such important items at the auction, why wasn’t it advertised so we could prepare more spirit stones? Why was it kept hidden?” An odd childlike voice sounded from one of the stone rooms.

Having already anticipated this question, the old man smiled and answered, “Fellow Daoist, don’t worry. The reason why the auction was kept a secret is that the owner of these three treasures are the same person and had personally made this request to the auction. As for why, I do not know, but the auction didn’t refuse it. However, I can guarantee that these treasures are genuine. Of course, since these headline treasures may have arrived on short notice, you may trade for these treasures using items of equivalent value. The items will be priced a tenth below the value that three of the market’s appraisal grandmasters and me give, so feel at ease!”

When they heard his reply, the cultivators felt a sense of amazement. Feeling overjoyed, they felt no further need to ask any questions.

Old Man Chi saw there were no more objections and promptly announced the start of the bid with a clap of his hands.

Over ten various colored lights promptly flew out onto the stage.

After the light faded, ten beautiful palace-robed women appeared from behind him.

Each woman possessed Core Formation cultivation and held a box of varying size.

“Following convention, we will begin the auction with finished goods and then move on to materials and secret techniques. The headline items will be auctioned last. For the first item of the auction, we have three bottles of the Brightheart Pills, cultivation progression medicine for Deity Transformation cultivators. Starting bid is three hundred thousand spirit stones with each increase being at least fifty thousand.” The white-robed old man waved his hand.

Suddenly, one of the women gracefully walked in front of him and raised her hand, opening the box to reveal three small jade bottles.

The old man waved his hand in front of the bottles and summoned one into his hand.

He skillfully opened it and tilted it, dropping a pure white crystalline pill into his hand.

Its dense medicinal sense immediately scattered.

The white-haired old man promptly held the pill in two of his fingers and waved it towards the cultivators.

An inconceivable event occurred.

The shining pill’s surface immediately released an azure and red glow. They were dazzling as if they were gems. And the air filled with its medicinal scent became several times stronger.

“I’ve already demonstrated the Brightheart Pill’s characteristics to you. I’m sure you don’t have any further doubts. You may begin the bid!”

“Three hundred fifty thousand!”

“Four hundred thousand!”

“Four hundred fifty!”

Suddenly, a large and a small ball of purple light appeared above the platform. It lit up to show the number of spirit stones on the current bid and which room the bidder was in.

From the start of the auction, the price surged. It appeared that these Deity Transformation cultivators had great uses for these spirit stones.

This was to be expected. Although the headline items were temping, a majority of cultivators couldn't hope to acquire them. It was better to take advantage of this opportunity to grab smaller items while the rich were distracted.

After Han Li returned to his abode, he would be able to refine the Clear Jade Pill and wouldn’t need to bid on similar items. He simply watched the bid until the pills were won for six hundred thousand spirit stones.

At that moment, many others had the same thoughts as Han Li: to quietly wait until the auction of the three headline items.

To tell the truth, Han Li was somewhat interested in the spirit treasure and the divine materials, but he wasn’t going to participate in the auction.

However, the main cultivation technique of the late Body Integration stage cultivator greatly tempted him.

Chapter 1352: Green Shadow

The azure-armored old man frowned and commanded, “Since the Foreign Spirit Plate has already sounded an alarm, we’ll need to investigate or else we’ll be punished when we return. Most foreign beings aren’t very powerful. So long as we’re careful, we should be able to take care of it smoothly.”

Since their Deity Transformation captain spoke, the rest of the squad kept silent, even if they were unwilling.

Soon after, the old man uttered a series of commands and the squad immediately split into several small groups before heading in the direction pointed by the Foreign Spirit Plate.

The squad of cultivators changed direction and flew off tens of kilometers.

They came across an unremarkable pile of stone and a purple miasma that seemed to surround the swamp.

The old man looked at the Foreign Spirit Plate in his hand and nodded. Then he waved his hand and commanded, “It appears to be there. We can’t let it escape.”

Suddenly, the black-armored guards splat out treasures to defend themselves and released their spiritual sense below.

After the time it took to finish a cup of tea, the cultivators; expression faintly changed.

“They’re a close distance away but our spiritual sense still can’t find them. It seems that we’ll only be able to personally search for them.” The old man took a deep breath and called out to the middle-aged man with narrow eyes, “Fellow Daoist Qin!”

“Don’t worry, Squad Leader. I know what to do.” The middle-aged man quickly replied. Soon after, he slapped the storage bracelet on his wrist and took out a pile of jet-black balls.

He raised his hand and scattered the balls underneath and began to chant.

A series of cracks sounded and the surface of the balls sparked with blue lightning. Their bodies morphed in the blink of an eye and they turned into fist-sized sparking bees. They were black and buzzed from their vibrating wings.

The others remained motionless in the air. Only the middle-aged man sat in midair with his hands forming an incantation. He formed an incantation gesture and over a hundred iron bees.

It appeared the patrolling cultivators took in the lessons of their predecessors and didn’t rashly drop to the ground where they would tangle with the foreign tribe in a messy situation.

Otherwise, with the strange unblockable tricks of foreign beings, they could find themselves dead in mutual destruction.

It would be better to control a few puppets to investigate.

Not only after the iron bees were released the Foreign Spirit Plates trembled and let out an exceptionally high-pitched shriek. A few of their plates even burst with blinding light, much to their shock.

The large fierce man looked at the spell plate in his hand and shouted, “Not good, the foreign being is near us. It’s already entered our hundred-meter perimeter.”

The others looked at their spell plates and were thrown into an uproar as they looked around them with wide eyes.

Within three hundred meters of them, above and below, they found nothing; it was completely empty.

“Everyone, quickly dispel its concealment! It will be over if it approaches us.” The old man shouted loudly, leaving a faint ringing in his subordinates’ ears. He then flipped his hand and produced a copper mirror.

The old man flung the copper mirror over his head and suddenly, it took the form of a bright moon. Light flashed from its surface and a bowl-sized azure beam shot out. It twirled around the moon before scattering in every direction.

The others began to unleash their own treasures to break the foreign being’s concealment, but the light found nothing.

However, the piercing shriek from the Foreign Spirit Plates only grew sharper. It was clear that it was already close.

At that moment, the cultivators revealed panic and the old man felt his face pale.

This situation was without a doubt because the foreign being or beings were scouts of the foreign tribes that shouldn’t be provoked. Not only did it not think to flee, but it thought to kill them instead.

As if squeezing his voice out from his throat, the old man shouted, “Quickly lay out the Elemental Spirit Light Formation! Common protections won’t protect us!”

Soon after, he paid no further attention to the mirror above his hand. He flipped his hand and summoned a red command token. He tossed it into the air and turned into a ball of flickering red light.

The other black-armored guards suddenly realized something and they released various magic tools into the air.

But at that moment, the magic tools slowed down.

Bang. Three of the Foreign Spirit Plates simultaneously erupted.

Above the owners of the three plates, several faint blurs suddenly appeared.

These silhouettes blurred as soon as they appeared and rushed towards the cultivators.

“Ah!”

The three black-armored cultivators finally discovered these grey silhouettes and couldn't help but shout. However, the magic treasure and spirit light protecting them didn’t block the blurs from entering their body.

Suddenly, they let out screams of pain and they fell to the ground as they covered their heads. It was unknown if they survived.

As soon as he saw the blurs, the old man’s face vastly changed and he hastily shouted, “They are shadow puppets from the Shadow Tribe! Quickly release your lightning-attribute treasures and techniques!”

Afterwards, he opened his mouth and spat out a silver-white flying sword.

Once the sword appeared, it covered the old man in silver-white lightning.

Afterwards, a grey shadow appeared right behind him, but thunder rang and a bolt of lightning shot out, flinging the shadow ten meters away.

The Shadow Tribe had an infamous reputation, and the cultivators immediately realized what was happening. However, only two of them were able to release their lightning-attribute treasure. The rest of them felt their bodies turn cold and they couldn't help but curse.

Lightning was an overbearing but rare element. Not many cultivators possess such a treasure.

The Shadow Tribe was also a bizarre race. Apart from lightning attributed treasures and a few peculiar techniques, nothing affected them.

And in their brief moment of hesitation, more grey shadows appeared beneath them.

The black-armored guards glanced at each other in terror and they shouted, scattering in streaks in every direction in an attempt to throw off the shadows.

However, the grey shadows seemed to truly become the cultivator’s shadow. They turned into streaks of grey light and relentlessly pursued the cultivators.

In the blink of an eye, the cultivators and the shadow puppets were a hundred meters away. All that remained in the original location was the old man and the other two black-armored guards that possessed a lightning treasure.

However, as time went on, an increasing number of grey shadows began to appear in front of them. There were now eight of them that were drifting around them, but rolls of lightning continued to hold them at bay.

However, these shadows didn’t seem to know pain since they continued to approach.

The old man took a deep breath and no longer concerned himself with the wellbeing of his subordinates. His wrist flashed with red light and suddenly produced a stack of talismans.

“Evil creatures, you’re courting death!”

The old man fiercely glared at them and approached one of the shadows. With a harsh expression, he released a talisman. It sharply crackled, releasing a dozen bolts of blue forking lightning at the grey image.

Rolls of thunder rang and lightning erupted. The grey shadow let out whimpers as a net of lightning surrounded it and turned it to dust.

The old man was overjoyed to see this. It seemed the hefty cost of these lightning talismans was well worth it.

He flipped his hand to produce another stack of talismans and released it in an attack.

But just as the forks of lightning was about to strike at another grey shadow, a cold snort sounded from all around them.

Meanwhile, the grey shadow suddenly produced a large green hand from the front of its body and its fingers blurred. The green hand somehow caught all the lightning in its hand.

After a series of muffled eruptions, the lightning disappeared without a trace.

“A green shadow!” The old man’s pupils shrunk.

“You all are courting death.” A cold emotionless voice sounded from the green hand. The hand trembled and twisted, turning into a green light silhouette.

The silhouette was in the shape of a person, but their head seemed extremely large, about two or three times larger than an ordinary human. The green light flickered from the face to reveal a pair of bright scarlet eyes.

It appeared to be a high-grade Shadow Tribe being as the old man expected. The old man’s lips twitched and his face turned blue.

Although lightning was effective on a majority of the Shadow Tribe, green shadows were at the same level as Deity Transformation-stage cultivators and their bodies were somewhat resistant to lightning. When a Deity Transformation cultivator and a green shadow fought, most of the time, the cultivator perished or lost.

And from the number of shadow puppets the green shadow could control, he feared that the green shadow was the highest of its grade.

The old man’s heart completely dropped.

At that moment, he heard distant eruptions from a distance. It was clear that the black-armored cultivators sank into a desperate battle.

The green shadow cared not for the old man’s terror and wordlessly took a step forward. His body strangely warped until he was a few meters away from the old man and he raised his arm towards the overbearing lightning surrounding the old man’s body.

He planned on directly grabbed ahold of the old man’s magic treasure.

The old man’s heart leapt. The green shadow was too fast. It was too late for him to dodge. He could only shout and pour the entirety of his magic power into his protective treasure.

The silver lightning thundered in front of him and grew three times thicker.

When the green shadow saw this, a trace of disdain appeared from his crimson eyes, and his palm continued forward. He reached out to grab the lightning.

Thunder rolled and the thick lightning bolt ruptured in a wild display, eventually revealing a small sword.

The small sword shifted its form continuously and wildly trembled, but the large green hand held firm.

The old man’s face became bloodlessly pale.

The green shadow let out a bewildering cackle and his body blurred as if he was about to take action.

But suddenly, thunder sounded above the old man and azure-white light flashed. A winged silhouette suddenly appeared.

As soon as the winged figure appeared, he wordlessly pointed his hands downward.